<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>The Judean People's Front</title>
 <link href="http://hyde.getpoole.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://hyde.getpoole.com/"/>
 <updated>2015-03-03T16:30:33-05:00</updated>
 <id>http://hyde.getpoole.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Brian Cohen</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Bazaar Logic</title>
   <link href="http://hyde.getpoole.com/2015/03/03/bazaar-logic/"/>
   <updated>2015-03-03T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://hyde.getpoole.com/2015/03/03/bazaar-logic</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Bibi had barely finished speaking before the criticism came rolling in:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;He said nothing new!&amp;quot; Complain those who previously were going crazy at the prospect that Bibi might reveal classified information about the deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;He gave talking points but no alternative to the deal,&amp;quot; say others with blinders on. &amp;quot;The prime minister didn&amp;#39;t offer any viable alternatives,&amp;quot; Obama said after skipping the speech and not even turning on the TV to listen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nancy Pelosi said she was so insulted by the &amp;quot;condescension,&amp;quot; that she was near tears. I would like to take a second remind her of Bibi&amp;#39;s actual words:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Israel is grateful for the support of American — of America’s people and of America’s presidents, from Harry Truman to Barack Obama... We appreciate all that President Obama has done for Israel. Now, some of that is widely known. And some of what the president has done for Israel might never be known, because it touches on some of the most sensitive and strategic issues that arise between an American president and an Israeli prime minister. But I know it, and I will always be grateful to President Obama for that support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That doesn&amp;#39;t sound condescending to me. It sounds incredibly respectful and appreciative. Later, as Bibi got into specifics, he was all policy, unlike his critics who leveled personal, ad hominem attacks against him (&lt;em&gt;cough&lt;/em&gt; J Street &lt;em&gt;cough&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the most striking criticism was &amp;quot;he wants us to go to war,&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;he wants to stop the diplomatic processes.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nothing could be further from the truth. So what did he really say?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now we’re being told that the only alternative to this bad deal is war. That’s just not true. The alternative to this bad deal is a much better deal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, if Iran threatens to walk away from the table — and this often happens in a Persian bazaar — call their bluff. They’ll be back, because they need the deal a lot more than you do. And by maintaining the pressure on Iran and on those who do business with Iran, you have the power to make them need it even more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/NV0siIR.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Persian Bazaar&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bibi understands #BazaarLogic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He knows that whether you&amp;#39;re in a Persian Bazaar, Arab Souk, or Hebrew Shuk, your strongest weapon is the threat that you might walk away. The second the seller thinks you won&amp;#39;t leave his stall without the item in question, you&amp;#39;ve already lost. You also need to be careful not to overplay this card or you end up like Abbas, who threatens to dismantle the PA every few months so no one takes the threat seriously. But if you haggle and go back and forth but make little progress, that&amp;#39;s when you say you&amp;#39;re done and start to walk. Before you know it, the seller is chasing you with a much better price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are obviously limits. If you offer a dollar for an intricate, hand-woven Persian rug, it doesn&amp;#39;t matter if you walk away because the seller would never accept such a paltry sum for his work. This is exactly what the Obama administration has been saying, &amp;quot;we can&amp;#39;t get a deal with complete disarmament or one that includes curbs on the ballistic missile program because Iran will never agree to one.&amp;quot; But if such restrictions are considered to be &amp;quot;too much&amp;quot; (something Obama didn&amp;#39;t agree with when he promised a nuclear-free Iran during the 2012 campaign), then Iran was never interested in negotiating to begin with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/EcOrSKs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Persian Carpet&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the opening of a bait and switch. You see a beautiful carpet hanging in a bazaar and the seller says he will only part with it in exchange for your first-born son, but if you&amp;#39;re interested, he has other carpets (lower quality, no doubt) in his shop if you&amp;#39;ll just step inside. Before you know it you&amp;#39;re caught up by the smells, vibrant colors, and fast talking merchant, remembering that you promised your wife you&amp;#39;d bring home a carpet no matter what, and instead of negotiating over the carpet you actually wanted, you&amp;#39;re haggling over one that you were never interested in to begin with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Iranians understand #BizaarLogic very well. It was their threats to walk away from negotiations that made the Obama administration run back to them with concession after concession. It was this threat that made Obama backtrack on his commitment to a nuclear-free Iran. It was this constantly looming threat to walk away, to leave Obama without his must-have deal, that excised any connection to the ballistic missile program and that caused Iranian hegemony to be spun as an asset rather than the greatest act of destabilization in the Middle East since the fall of the Ottoman Empire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/DNfOq7H.png&quot; alt=&quot;Bibi in Congress&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prime Minister Netanyahu was right on the money when he said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My friends, for over a year, we’ve been told that no deal is better than a bad deal. Well, this is a bad deal. It’s a very bad deal. We’re better off without it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s time we let the Iranians know we&amp;#39;re done negotiating a bad deal (not any deal, but a bad deal) and if they are interested in real negotiations, they should tell us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But until then, the sanctions will increase and strengthen as we turn around and walk out of their Bazaar.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Blue-and-Whitewashing: Using Jews to cover up Anti-Semitism</title>
   <link href="http://hyde.getpoole.com/2015/03/02/blue-and-whitewashing/"/>
   <updated>2015-03-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://hyde.getpoole.com/2015/03/02/blue-and-whitewashing</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3&gt;Using Jews to cover up Anti-Semitism&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;re the type of person who is reading this blog (you poor unfortunate soul), chances are you&amp;#39;ve heard of the term &amp;quot;Jew-washing.&amp;quot; This term - coined by Yitzak Santis and Gerald M. Steinberg of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ngo-monitor.org/&quot;&gt;NGO Monitor&lt;/a&gt; in their article &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thejewishweek.com/editorial-opinion/opinion/jew-washing-and-bds&quot;&gt;On ‘Jew-Washing’ And BDS: How Jewish anti-Israel activists are gaining influence among Christian groups.&lt;/a&gt; - is the pro-Israel attempt to fight fire with fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The BDS crowd has already had lots of success with &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://mondoweiss.net/2011/11/a-documentary-guide-to-brand-israel-and-the-art-of-pinkwashing&quot;&gt;pink-washing&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;quot; - accusing Israel of treating LGBT citizens as human beings solely for propaganda purposes - and is working on getting &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theislamicmonthly.com/an-interfaith-trojan-horse-faithwashing-apartheid-and-occupation/&quot;&gt;faith-washing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; - the idea that Israel is trying to get Muslims to betray their faith by simply talking to Israelis - the same success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Santis and Steinberg do wonderful work defending Israel from organizations hell-bent on demonizing, delegitimizing, and destroying the Jewish state. They are great scholars and attorneys, but PR execs they are not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, while Jew-washing may technically fit the mold, it really sounds like it belongs in a mikvah. (h/t/ &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/AnarchoZionist/status/564261462474907650&quot;&gt;@AnarchoZionist&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/7at15HS.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Just your typical mikvah&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we here at The Judean People&amp;#39;s Front decided to help them out and came up with a term that we feel works much better:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Blue-and-Whitewashing&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/R2YVOJR.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Blue-and-Whitewashing&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;So what is #BlueAndWhitewashing anyway?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;covering up or glossing over the anti-Semitism of a group or individual by citing support from a small group of Jews.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is typically done by anti-Zionist organizations who point to their buddies at Jewish Voice for Peace, Mondoweiss, or the Neturei Karta to say, &amp;quot;We&amp;#39;re not anti-Semitic, just look at all the Jews who agree with us!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why is a term like this even necessary? In order to answer that, we need look no further than the creator of the term &amp;quot;pink-washing,&amp;quot; Sarah Schulman. A &amp;quot;Distinguished Professor&amp;quot; of the Humanities at the College of Staten Island (your bubbe would be proud, though as &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tabletmag.com/jewish-news-and-politics/134712/pinkwashing-sarah-schulman?all=1&quot;&gt;James Kirchick of Tablet&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://elderofziyon.blogspot.com/2013/06/sarah-schulman-of-pinkwashing-fame-is.html#.VPCKVnx4qrg&quot;&gt;Elder of Ziyon&lt;/a&gt; have pointed out, she only has a mail-order Bachelor&amp;#39;s Degree from Empire State College, hardly an academic resume for a Distinguished Professor), Schulman, a lesbian and Israel-hater (which are by no means normally connected), needed to find a way to combine her two passions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But she ran into a problem: if she actually cares about gay rights, how can she hate the only country in the Middle East that actually protects the rights and freedoms of its LGBT community? How can she fight for the Palestinians when they routinely murder gays to the point that &lt;a href=&quot;http://forward.com/articles/1125/for-gay-palestinians-tel-aviv-is-mecca/&quot;&gt;most Outed Palestinians must seek refuge in Israel&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/oqA8lYF.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Homocrites&quot; title=&quot;(h/t ElderOfZiyon)&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not to be undone by the facts, Schulman concluded that it wasn&amp;#39;t she who was wrong (shocker, I know) but Israel. Israel doesn&amp;#39;t actually care about gay rights, it only has pro-gay policies in order to distract the world from its horrible crimes against the Palestinians. Really, Israel exaggerates how open it is and in doing so, reduces its gay community to nothing more than pawns in its Hasbara machine. Sure there may be some &amp;quot;issues&amp;quot; with being gay in the Arab world, but really these are trending down and once Israel is destroyed, Arabs will surely embrace their gay brothers as they dance together on the graves of the Zionists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If this sounds ridiculous to you, congratulations, you&amp;#39;re still able to distinguish fact from fiction and right from wrong, but then again, Blue-and-Whitewashers rarely use solid logic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what I think I found the most interesting, was that Schulman herself is an open pink-washer! According to her fan, &lt;a href=&quot;(http://www.gilad.co.uk/writings/israelpalestine-and-the-queer-international-a-book-review-by.html)&quot;&gt;self-proclaimed Jewish anti-Semite Gilad Atzmon&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But she is also interested in promoting her ‘queer political agenda’. For Schulman, &lt;strong&gt;Palestinians are simply a means toward her sacred progressive end&lt;/strong&gt;. &amp;quot;If people like me are going to turn our backs on [Israeli] queer events in support of the boycott [BDS], then we must be assured that the boycott both recognizes queer support and acknowledges Palestinian LGBT organizing,” she writes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To Schulman, Palestinians are just &amp;quot;a means toward&amp;quot; an end. They are pawns that she uses for her own misguided &amp;quot;gay&amp;quot; agenda (I use quotes because she is not representative of the LGBT community and talking of some &amp;quot;Gay Agenda&amp;quot; makes me supremely uncomfortable). So in reality, Schulman is doing exactly what she is accusing the Israeli government of doing, except she is doing it for real! But I guess this won&amp;#39;t be the first or the last time the anti-Israel (&lt;em&gt;cough&lt;/em&gt; anti-Semitic &lt;em&gt;cough&lt;/em&gt;) crowd engages in hypocrisy. What is different here, is that some Palestinians, like academic Joseph Massad, have noticed and complain that she is imposing a &amp;#39;Western concept of sexuality on Palestinian men.&amp;#39; This form of a cultural imperialism of the mind (never thought I&amp;#39;d write those words before) would surely be condemned by Schulman in any other context, but since it promotes her own agenda, it&amp;#39;s a-okay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;But she&amp;#39;s just one person, who made up one catchy phrase, why should I care about her?&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should care because she is on the advisory board of the ironically named Jewish Voice for Peace. She is the &amp;quot;Jewish&amp;quot; voice that is pushing for anything but peace. It is voices like Shulman&amp;#39;s who &lt;a href=&quot;http://proisraelbaybloggers.blogspot.com/2014/11/jewish-voice-for-peace-finding-common.html&quot;&gt;advocate support for terrorists like Rasmea Odeh&lt;/a&gt; and support the BDS movement to destroy Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s more, she is the Faculty Advisor for Students for Justice in Palestine at the College of Staten Island. She provides the same hateful guidance to SJP as she does for JVP and that shouldn&amp;#39;t be a surprise. The only reason why JVP gets more support from the wider Jewish community (but thankfully, still mostly on the liberal fringes) is because it sounds tamer than SJP, but in reality they share the same goals and tactics: the destruction of the State of Israel through intimidation and terror.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In reality, it should really be called Jewish Voice for Palestine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/hm57JAG.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jewish Voice for Palestine&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the constant refrain from Arab anti-Zionists that Semites can&amp;#39;t be anti-Semites, we know this is not the case. Just ask &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ynetnews.com/articles/0,7340,L-4106265,00.html&quot;&gt;Gilad &amp;quot;Jews control the world&amp;quot; Atzmon&lt;/a&gt;, who, as it turns out, wrote a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gilad.co.uk/writings/israelpalestine-and-the-queer-international-a-book-review-by.html&quot;&gt;mostly fawning review&lt;/a&gt; of one of her books. While Schulman is more careful not to specifically target Jews without using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dog-whistle_politics&quot;&gt;dog-whistle&lt;/a&gt; of Zionism, you don&amp;#39;t have to dig very deep to see her hatred not just of Israel but of the Jewish people and her acceptance of classic anti-Semitic conspiracy theories. Not only that, but she herself talks about her own transformation from a “Jewish, lesbian New Yorker” into a “Cosmopolitan queer and avid BDS advocate,” that is to say how she stopped being a closed-minded Jew and opened herself up to the idea of global solidarity with hatred of Israel at its core.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her obsessive focus on demonizing Israel and her desire to destroy the world&amp;#39;s only Jewish State (not to mention the only safe haven for gays in the Middle East) while completely ignoring all other countries, especially ones right next door that routinely arrest, torture, and murder gays and other minorities, is only attributable to a deep-seated hatred of her own people. But more surprisingly (well, not really, considering all we know of her) is the way she buys into the classic anti-Semitic canard of a Jewish/Israeli cabal running world events. When confronted by Jayson Littman, the Gay Jewish Zionist behind &lt;a href=&quot;www.myhebro.com&quot;&gt;MyHebro.com&lt;/a&gt;, Schulman absolutely loses it. According to Kirchick:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a November 2012 interview with the British lesbian magazine &lt;em&gt;Diva&lt;/em&gt;, Schulman said that “the more I work in this arena, the more aware I become of the involvement of the Israeli government in the US LGBT community.” She named Littman, among others, as “Israeli government operatives … who work for the Foreign Ministry, whose job it is to work our community along pinkwashing lines.” Among their tasks, she said, are to “plant stories in newspapers, co-opt our events … and flood websites with propaganda.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see? Littman is just a secret pinkwashing agent on a mission to dominate the media, control the actions of an entire community, and does so on orders from the Jews... sorry, I mean Israel. Isn&amp;#39;t it such an interesting coincidence that so many anti-Israel conspiracy theories fit so perfectly with ancient libels against the Jews with just one word changed?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But getting back to the original matter of pinkwashing, I&amp;#39;m sure there are some of you who are thinking: but aren&amp;#39;t some Blue-and-Whitewashers really just against the occupation and not against the State of Israel itself?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well I suppose it is possible that some rank and file B&amp;amp;Wers believe this at first, but those at the top, especially Schulman, are 100% against the existence of the world&amp;#39;s only Jewish State in any borders (and use their positions to influence those beneath them). She is outspoken against the &amp;quot;crime of normalization,&amp;quot; that is treating Israel like a normal country by engaging with it in even the most mild of ways. The threat of normalization is what led &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.palwatch.org/main.aspx?fi=157&amp;amp;doc_id=12585&quot;&gt;PA officials to declare a soccer game between Israeli and Palestinian children a war crime&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Gilad &amp;quot;I support burning synagogues&amp;quot; Atzmon, &amp;quot;Schulman actually provides us with a unique and invaluable window into Jewish secular progressive thought.&amp;quot; So it should be no surprise then that Schulman&amp;#39;s disciples over at Jewish Voice for Palestine are also active in the premiere, more &amp;quot;mainstream&amp;quot; anti-Israel, anti-peace group for Jewish secular progressives, J Street.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At J Street&amp;#39;s 2011 Conference, Jewish Voice for Palestine&amp;#39;s Executive Director Rebecca Vilkomerson, &lt;a href=&quot;http://jewishvoiceforpeace.org/blog/remarks-at-j-streets-bds-panel&quot;&gt;was invited to speak at a panel discussion of the BDS movement&lt;/a&gt;. The idea that a group professing to be &amp;quot;pro-Israel&amp;quot; would host a discussion on whether or not Israel should exist is just astounding... unless of course you know anything about J Street. Most Blue-and-Whitewashing BDSers claim to merely be &amp;quot;against the occupation&amp;quot; and point to the fact that the BDS movement calls for &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bdsmovement.net/bdsintro&quot;&gt;Ending [Israel&amp;#39;s] occupation and colonization of &lt;strong&gt;all Arab lands occupied in June 1967&lt;/strong&gt; and dismantling the Wall&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;quot; But what they won&amp;#39;t tell you is that the movement&amp;#39;s original Mission Statement, drafted in 2005, calls for &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bdsmovement.net/call#sthash.iy3Vra4H.dpuf&quot;&gt;Ending its occupation and colonization of &lt;strong&gt;all Arab lands&lt;/strong&gt; and dismantling the Wall&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt; and this has only been changed in English to make it sound more palatable to Western ears. But of course their third goal, &amp;quot;Respecting, protecting and promoting the rights of Palestinian refugees to return to their homes and properties as stipulated in UN resolution 194,&amp;quot; which essentially calls for the end of the Jewish State, has neve been altered, amended, or abrogated. While the BDS movement and their Blue-and-Whitewashing pawns are getting better at PR, their goals are just as nefarious as ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, when it comes to Schulman&amp;#39;s agenda, even Gilad &amp;quot;maybe the &lt;em&gt;Protocols of the Elders of Zion&lt;/em&gt; is real&amp;quot; Atzmon, doesn&amp;#39;t even fully believe her. Since Omar Barghouti - the Kuwaiti-born, Egyptian-raised, &amp;quot;Palestinian&amp;quot; PhD student at and graduate of Tel Aviv University who is leading the the global BDS campaign (did that make your head hurt as much as mine?) - was initially opposed to welcoming Queer support for BDS (either because of his own or Palestinian society&amp;#39;s homophibia) Schulman beilieves she was able to win him over saying, “now I know that there is a significant Palestinian ‘civil society’ that supports a nonviolent strategy for change and is feminist and now pro-gay.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is too much for even Gilad &amp;quot;the Jews killed Jesus&amp;quot; Atzmon:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am very impressed with this revelation about a leading Palestinian civil society becoming ‘pro-gay’ and ‘feminist. I guess that &lt;strong&gt;Soros and his institutions&lt;/strong&gt; indeed have reason to be optimistic about their chance to change the face of the Arab society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;However, I would really like to know whether the Palestinians are aware of all this.&lt;/strong&gt; For some reason I have a feeling that, as in the case of BDS surreptitiously changing its goals statement, &lt;strong&gt;the same Palestinian civil society now has become ‘pro-gay’ and ‘feminist’ without anyone in Palestine knowing about it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Gilad &amp;quot;the Holocaust is the new Jewish religion&amp;quot; Atzmon makes sure to get in his &amp;quot;Jews control the world&amp;quot; conspiracy theory by talking about &amp;quot;Soros and his institutions,&amp;quot; he just can&amp;#39;t accept that Palestinians are actually pro-gay. Even this hateful anti-Semite recognizes the rampant homophobia in Palestinian and Arab society and can&amp;#39;t believe that has change just because Schulman says so. It would be nice if he he applied this critical thinking to, well, anything else, but hey, it&amp;#39;s a start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fact of the matter is that both feminists and the LGBT community deserve better leaders than the likes of Sarah Schulman, but since many of those leaders are in fact Israeli, they&amp;#39;ll merely be smeared as pinkwashing and never get their chance to lead and better their communities. That&amp;#39;s because Pinkwashers and Blue-and-Whitewashers like Schulman don&amp;#39;t actually care about gays or Palestinians, they are just consumed with a hatred of Israel and Jews that takes over their entire being.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just because someone is named Sarah Miriam Schulman doesn&amp;#39;t mean we should sit back and take it while she uses her name to Blue-and-Whitewash anti-Semitism of the worst order. These Blue-and-Whitewashers should be named, shamed, and called what they really are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Traitors and Anti-Semites.&lt;/h3&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>About the Palestinian "Refugees"</title>
   <link href="http://hyde.getpoole.com/2015/02/26/about-palestinian-refugees/"/>
   <updated>2015-02-26T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://hyde.getpoole.com/2015/02/26/about-palestinian-refugees</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h5&gt;Should Israel let them &amp;quot;come back?&amp;quot;(hint: It already has!) &lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is impossible to have a discussion about Israel today without someone bringing up the Palestinian &amp;quot;refugees.&amp;quot; This is due to two reasons that are important to understand:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most people, being good and compassionate (he said not fully convinced) but not knowing much about the situation (he said more confidently), hear the word &amp;quot;refugee&amp;quot; and can be forgiven for automatically thinking, &amp;quot;hey, why can&amp;#39;t they just go home?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Arab leadership knows about number one and has decided to cynically exploit both those emotions and lack of knowledge while the Palestinians and Israel are left to pay the price.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if we&amp;#39;re going to have a real discussion about these people, we need to get passed the emotion and look at the facts of history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;How did the Palestinians come to be Refugees in the first place?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Palestinian &amp;quot;refugees&amp;quot; were created after Israel accepted but the Palestinian and Arab leadership rejected two peaceful offers of partition: &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peel_Commission&quot;&gt;the Peel Partition in 1937&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Nations_Partition_Plan_for_Palestine&quot;&gt;UN Partition of Palestine in 1947&lt;/a&gt;. Had either of these been accepted there would have been no refugees and no wars (and in the case of Peel, millions of Jews would have had a safe haven available to escape the Holocaust). Instead of accepting the peace proposals or offering their own alternatives (other than total domination and extermination), the Palestinians and Arabs responded with rejection, riots, and war.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This rejectionism, coupled with violence, was the cause that started the refugee crisis.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Did Israel create the refugee crisis?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contrary to what Palestinian propagandists claim, there was no organized or official plan by the Israeli government to expel the Palestinians. The general policy was the allow each military commander to make the decision whether to allow Palestinians who came under their control to stay or not. According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://larryjhs.fastmail.fm.user.fm/The%20Birth%20of%20the%20Palestinian%20Refugee%20Problem%20Revisited.pdf&quot;&gt;Benny Morris&lt;/a&gt;, &amp;quot;Only an extremely small, almost insignificant number of the refugees during this early period left because of Haganah or IZL or LHI expulsion orders or forceful ‘advice’ to that effect.&amp;quot; (p.139). The result was generally that Arab towns that didn&amp;#39;t resist were allowed to stay, while those that served as bases of attack were often expelled. However there were cases where some villages were forced out without resisting due to their strategic positions on supply roads and there were also cases of towns that, once subdued, were allowed to stay despite their belligerent past. Because of this policy, over one hundred thousand Arabs remained in Israel at the end of the war and their descendants make up Israel&amp;#39;s 1.5 million-strong Israeli-Arab minority.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember, unlike every Arab neighbor, Israel didn&amp;#39;t build a single refugee camp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, there were situations like the one that arose in Haifa. The Arab leadership of Haifa fled very early on and, after the city fell to Israel, no Arab was willing to publicly state that they should stay in the Jewish state for fear of being labeled a traitor. So, abandoned by their leadership and captives of the rabid anti-Semitism they had been fed for decades, 70,000 Arabs (nearly 1/10 of all Palestinian refugees) packed up and left, most after the military threat was gone (though admittedly still fresh in their minds) and &lt;a href=&quot;http://emperors-clothes.com/docs/haifa.htm&quot;&gt;against the active entreaties of the local Jewish population&lt;/a&gt;, including &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2008/05/04/books/review/Margolick-t.html?pagewanted=all&amp;amp;_r=0&quot;&gt;the Jewish Mayor of Haifa,&lt;/a&gt; to stay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is all in stark contrast to the officially stated and practiced goals of the Arab armies and this fact contributed to the fear that compelled many Palestinians to leave. Every single time a Jewish town was overtaken by Arab armies (like &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kfar_Etzion_massacre&quot;&gt;Gush Etzion&lt;/a&gt;), the population was either expelled or massacred. Knowing that this was their own policy, many Palestinian villagers assumed the Jews would do the same to them and fled before the Haganah even reached their towns. Thankfully the Arabs were only able to conquer a few towns, so the numbers of Jewish refugees from Judea, Samaria, and Gaza was limited to a few thousand. These refugees included the non-Zionist population of eastern Jerusalem in keeping with Jordanian policy to ethnically cleanse the holy city of all Jews. From 1949-1967, no Jew (or, for that matter, Israeli Muslim or Christian) was allowed to visit the Old City and Jewish holy sites were destroyed and desecrated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/UXKsBQo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Hurva Synagogue&quot; title=&quot;Arab Legion soldier within the ruins, after the Legion blew it up for no reason. Behind him, remnants of the eastern wall show a painted fresco of Mount Sinai and two arched tablets symbolising the Ten Commandments. June 1948&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is interesting that while people are constantly saying Palestinians need to return to their homes, when Jews move back to the West Bank there is international outcry and condemnation...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Were the Palestinians the only Refugees?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the thousands of Jewish refugees from Judea, Samaria, and Gaza, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jewish_exodus_from_Arab_and_Muslim_countries&quot;&gt;over 850,000 Jews from Muslim countries&lt;/a&gt; were forced out or compelled to leave at the same time. Unlike the Palestinians, these Jews were not recognized as refugees, were offered no international aid, and weren&amp;#39;t even in a war zone. The only reason why these people are not refugees today is because they were taken in by Israel and given citizenship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/EoKSHix.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Yemenite Jews&quot; title=&quot;Yemenite Jews en route from Aden to Israel, during Operation Magic Carpet (1949–1950)&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Why are Palestinians still refugees?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This gets to the real heart of the problem: the only reason Palestinians are refugees today is because &lt;strong&gt;the Arab states refused to resettle them&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;the United Nations went along with it&lt;/strong&gt;. Only Jordan gave them citizenship, but still insisted they stay in refugee camps. This led to a situation in which many people were often only living a few miles from their previous homes, in a completely identical society, and yet were prevented from rebuilding their lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The refusal of the Arab states to resettle the Palestinians by forcing them to remain in refugee camps is only reason why Palestinian refugees exist today.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every single war in human history has created refugees, and yet the Israeli War of Independence is the only one that has created perpetual refugees. In 1923 &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Population_exchange_between_Greece_and_Turkey%20exchanged%201.85%20million%20refugees&quot;&gt;Greece and Turkey&lt;/a&gt;, all of which were resettled. During WWII, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Belgian_refugees#Second_World_War&quot;&gt;roughly 2 million Belgians&lt;/a&gt; became refugees but were resettled and after the war, [12-14 million Germans](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flight&lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt;expulsion&lt;em&gt;of&lt;/em&gt;Germans_(1944%E2%80%9350) became refugees but were resettled (with some 500-600,000 dying en route). 1946 saw &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.globalsecurity.org/military/world/war/forced-population-transfers.htm&quot;&gt;200,000 Hungarians and an equal number of Slovaks&lt;/a&gt; cross borders as refugees before being resettled. Between 1944-1953 1.24 million Poles became refugees before settling in the new Poland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1947, &lt;strong&gt;the same year that the First Arab-Israeli War started&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Partition_of_India#Resettlement_of_refugees_in_India:_1947.E2.80.931957&quot;&gt;India and Pakistan were also partitioned&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;creating 14.52 million refugees and roughly 1 million migration related deaths&lt;/strong&gt;. At 7.23 million, the number of Muslim refugees created was almost exactly 10x the number of Palestinians created at the exact same time. Yet for some reason (&lt;em&gt;cough&lt;/em&gt; no Jews to blame &lt;em&gt;cough&lt;/em&gt;) there was no real outcry over this in the Muslim world, no refugee camps remain, and no international agencies needed to be established to care for them. The Palestinians - and only the Palestinians - are perpetual refugees who refuse and are refused permanent resettlement in direct defiance of the goals of the United Nations High Commissioner of Refugees, but perfectly in line with the rules and goals of their own personal UN aid agency, UNRWA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Would you let them into your country?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, let&amp;#39;s put all this aside and say refugees have traditionally always be allowed to return, even their great-grandchildren, which we&amp;#39;ve shown is not the case; would you accept into your country a population greater than your own that is not only openly committed to your destruction but has been actively working towards it for 100 years? Would any sane country accept this? If India and Pakistan go to war again and India insists on moving 200,000 Hindus into Pakistan as a condition for peace, would Pakistan accept that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More to the point, if the goal is supposed to be Two States for Two Peoples (as we&amp;#39;re constantly told it is), then why do Palestinians insist on moving to Israel instead of a future Palestine? Shouldn&amp;#39;t the State of Palestine be where the refugees resettle? Years ago, when I first heard about this, being a good liberal Jewish youngster, I was convinced I was listening to extreme right-wing Israeli propaganda. The only reason it doesn&amp;#39;t surprise me anymore is because I now recognize that this is being advocated not to help &amp;quot;alleviate Palestinian suffering&amp;quot; or out of a sense of &amp;quot;justice&amp;quot; for refugees, but because such a move would destroy the Jewish State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Let&amp;#39;s Flip the Equation: &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What would the world&amp;#39;s reaction be if Israel said it would agree to a Two-State Solution but only if it could continue to build settlements in the Palestinian state to house millions of Jews?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Does that sound ridiculous? It should. But that is exactly what the Palestinians are insisting on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Who is responsible for the creating the Palestinian refugees?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The way I see it, the blame for creating the Palestinian refugees is shared by the Palestinians, the Arab states, and yes, by Israel. Many Israelis get upset when I mention that we are also responsible for the refugees, but the fact that we are partially responsible is undeniable. We were justified in establishing our state and we didn&amp;#39;t have a policy to simply &amp;quot;expel the Arabs&amp;quot; (in direct contrast to the Arabs&amp;#39; policy of expelling or killing all Jews), but our actions still helped cause the refugee situation (and as I showed above, this was and is a constant by-product of war, not something unique to Israel).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that we recognize that Israel is responsible for 1/3 of the refugee situation, we should ask ourselves, is there something can Israel do about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When someone asks you this, you should tell them that Israel has actually already fulfilled any obligation it has towards the Palestinian refugees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;What? How could this be, you say. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://soc.haifa.ac.il/%7Es.smooha/download/TheModelofDemIsraelasJewDeminNN.pdf&quot;&gt;Professor Sammy Smooha of Haifa University&lt;/a&gt; (p.487), between 1967 and 2001, &lt;strong&gt;Israel took in roughly 250,000 Palestinians&lt;/strong&gt; under the laws of Family Reunification &lt;strong&gt;and gave them citizenship&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You read that correctly, &lt;strong&gt;Israel has already taken in more than 1/3 the number of original refugees&lt;/strong&gt;. If Israel shares 1/3 of the responsibility for the Palestinian refugees and has already taken in more than 1/3 the number of refugees, what more should be expected of it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Why have you never heard about this before?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn&amp;#39;t so clear. But it is likely due to the fact that since the Palestinians insist on their &amp;quot;Right of Return,&amp;quot; which would overwhelm Israel with millions of hostile new citizens, Israel is wary of giving this claim any legitimacy. By saying Israel has already taken in hundreds of thousand of Palestinians, Israel worries this would allow the Palestinians to say &amp;quot;if you took in 250,000, why not more?&amp;quot; However, since the Palestinians are insisting on the full &amp;quot;Right of Return&amp;quot; anyway, I see no reason why this fact should stay hidden and why Israel&amp;#39;s supporters can&amp;#39;t champion the unprecedented steps Israel has already taken in this regard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is actually very ironic because, nowadays, the only time this is brought up is when anti-Israel activists smear Israel for not allowing the Palestinian spouses of Israelis move to Israel (the law was amended in 2001 after numerous Palestinian spouses engaged in terrorism after gaining Israeli citizenship). They are quick to denounce Israel for refusing to allow Palestinian wives and husbands to move to Israel but never say a word about the fact that over 250,000 already have. They also never mention that should a Palestinian state ever come into being, the Palestinians have already said that no Jews would be allowed to live there, whether they are spouses of Palestinians or not. But I doubt any of you are shocked by this hypocrisy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So without even getting into the more controversial topics of where the Palestinians actually came from and how long they were even living in Mandatory Palestine to begin with, it is clear that they are unique only in their perpetual status as refugees (not caused by Israel) and Israel has already fulfilled any obligations it may have had for their resettlement.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
