<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title></title>
		<description>I asked for a media empire, but the Elders of Zion only gave me a Twitter account and a blog.</description>
		<link>http://judeanpf.com</link>
		<atom:link href="http://judeanpf.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>The Many Myths of Jerusalem: Part 2</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Part two of our multipart series on &lt;strong&gt;The Many Myths of Jerusalem&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Myth Number 2: East Jerusalem&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stories reported from Israel&amp;#39;s capital are routinely described as being from East Jerusalem, Arab East Jerusalem, or Israeli Occupied Arab East Jerusalem (that&amp;#39;s our favorite one). This is taken for granted by most people who think, &amp;quot;why shouldn&amp;#39;t a report from East Jerusalem be labeled as such?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The answer is simple: &lt;strong&gt;East Jerusalem is a modern myth with no basis in history.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Where does the myth of &amp;quot;East&amp;quot; Jerusalem come from?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We already know that many of the areas in Jerusalem have never even been considered to be part of the city to begin with from &lt;a href=&quot;http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/10/Jerusalem-Myth-01/&quot;&gt;Part 1&lt;/a&gt;, so let&amp;#39;s examine how the term &amp;quot;East&amp;quot; Jerusalem itself came into being.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Birth of the term &amp;quot;East&amp;quot; Jerusalem&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1f/Divided_Jerusalem_P1010019.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;E Jlem&quot;&gt;
This one is actually pretty straightforward and relatively well-known: From 1948 to 1967 the city of Jerusalem was divided for the first time in its history. Not only was it divided, but the Arab conquest brought with it a destruction of Jewish lives and holy sites at a level unseen in the city since the Crusades. Previous riots in the city did lead to widespread death and injury of Jews, but Zionists put up resistance and eventually the British were able to quell the violence... it just happens that after doing so and recognizing the riots were merely Arab pogroms against Jews, the British chose to appease the Arabs and punish the victims by restricting Jewish rights and immigration quotas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under Jordanian Occupation, the city was not made the capital (it was the &amp;quot;Second Capital&amp;quot; in name only, no administrative offices were moved or created) and while Muslim pilgrims continued to visit - unlike Jews who were barred by law - most major Muslim religious and political leaders ignored the city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/L7hbbTz.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Barbed Wire&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since Jerusalem was divided (if for only a very short period of time) it was necessary to differentiate between to two parts and the simplest way to do so was by the characterizing them as East and West. But this gave rise to the idea that they were actually two separate cities, which persisted after 1967. Under normal circumstances, once divided cities are reunited, people stop referring to the two halves as separate. But of course, since Jews are involved, the world can&amp;#39;t countenance that in Jerusalem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Division of Jerusalem was a Blip in History&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1c/Divided_Jerusalem_P1010014.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Migdal David&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The oldest section of Jerusalem, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/City_of_David#Chalcolithic_.284500.E2.80.933500_BCE.29&quot;&gt;the City of David&lt;/a&gt; dates back to the Chalcolithic Period, roughly 6500 years ago, and while archaeology from that time is not really definitive in terms of political structure, it&amp;#39;s safe to assume such a small settlement was not divided in half.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So out of a history of 6500 years, the city of Jerusalem was only divided for 19 years. &lt;strong&gt;That&amp;#39;s less than .3% of its history!&lt;/strong&gt; Even if you&amp;#39;re only counting from 3000 years ago, &lt;strong&gt;that&amp;#39;s barely .6% of its history.&lt;/strong&gt; Such a small blip wouldn&amp;#39;t even register in the history books, but we&amp;#39;re supposed to accept that this is the way it should now be forever?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone who says Jerusalem must be divided has to answer a simple question: why should a 19-year aberration be used as a guide for a permanent settlement?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Russian East Berlin&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When was the last time you heard a journalist refer to Russian East Berlin? I doubt you can find a reference after 1989 when the Wall fell. The unification of Berlin was celebrated throughout the world as the harbinger of the fall of the Soviet Union and the triumph of the West. No one questioned the city&amp;#39;s reunification despite the fact that it had been two cities for 41 years (more than twice as long as Jerusalem was divided).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a newly resurgent Russia, led by Vladimir Putin, pushes through Eastern Europe, NATO, the EU, and the US seem unwilling to stand up to this international bully. But what would their reaction be if he said in any peace deal with the West, Russia needs to have East Berlin as its regional capital? Would anyone accept such a brazen and outlandish demand?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course not, but this is exactly what is happening in Jerusalem!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;&amp;quot;Arab&amp;quot; East Jerusalem&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Journalists often add the qualifier &amp;quot;Arab&amp;quot; to the beginning when referring to &amp;quot;East Jerusalem.&amp;quot; This is not a descriptive term, but rather a political one. In the 1990s, there was &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/East_Jerusalem#Demographics&quot;&gt;a Jewish majority&lt;/a&gt; in eastern Jerusalem, but this didn&amp;#39;t stop the press from describing it as &amp;quot;Arab East Jerusalem.&amp;quot; Why? Because the press is fully committed to a redivision of the city. Since the 90&amp;#39;s the Jewish population has fallen a little below the 50% mark, but a truly descriptive term would be &amp;quot;Mixed eastern Jerusalem&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Jewish-Arab eastern Jerusalem&amp;quot; since the populations nearly balanced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Journalists usually refer to Haifa as a mixed Jewish-Arab city even though Arabs make up roughly 10% of the population, so why wouldn&amp;#39;t they refer to &amp;quot;East Jerusalem&amp;quot; as mixed when Jews make up nearly 50%? Because that would help strengthen Israel&amp;#39;s claim the eastern portion of its capital and that goes against the narrative of the Western Media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3a/Divided_Jerusalem_-_Western_Wall_P1010043.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Western Wall&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;eastern Jerusalem&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is clear that the use of the term &amp;quot;East Jerusalem&amp;quot; is politically motivated and designed to prevent the permanent reunification of the city. Unfortunately, the term has become so pervasive that even Israelis use it today. But that doesn&amp;#39;t mean that we should!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When discussing the eastern parts of the city, it is best to talk about &amp;quot;eastern Jerusalem&amp;quot; with a lowercase &amp;quot;e.&amp;quot; This makes it clear you are discussing a section of a city, not a separate city. Terminology is incredibly important as it is what frames the debate. If we accept the Palestinian names that were created to overshadow or erase the Jewish connection to Israel, we have already lost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;More Myths Are Coming!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check back soon for the next installment of our series on the Many Myths of Jerusalem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/10/Jerusalem-Myth-01/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Part 1: The Internationalization of Jerusalem&lt;/em&gt; here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/20/Jerusalem-Myth-02/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/20/Jerusalem-Myth-02/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Explaining Bibi&#39;s &#39;The Arabs are Voting&#39; to the West</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Now that Netanyahu&amp;#39;s victory has been accepted (grudgingly) as fact by the media, there has been a rush to explain the how this possibly could have happened. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesofisrael.com/after-electoral-trouncing-what-future-for-the-israeli-left/#ixzz3UkcCRE4a&quot;&gt;Haviv Rettig Gur of the Times of Israel&lt;/a&gt; pointed out that despite its loss, the &amp;quot;Israeli left, to be sure, did better than it has done in almost a generation,&amp;quot; before explaining not only why it wasn&amp;#39;t enough, but what they could do differently. But the Israel haters over at Haaretz and the New York Times were interested in no such introspection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2015/03/18/opinion/an-israeli-election-turns-ugly.html?hp&amp;amp;action=click&amp;amp;pgtype=Homepage&amp;amp;module=c-column-top-span-region&amp;amp;region=c-column-top-span-region&amp;amp;WT.nav=c-column-top-span-region&quot;&gt;An Israeli Election Turns Ugly&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; declared the NYTimes editorial board:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s outright &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2015/03/17/world/middleeast/benjamin-netanyahu-campaign-settlement.html&quot;&gt;rejection of a Palestinian state&lt;/a&gt; and his &lt;strong&gt;racist rant &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2015/03/18/world/middleeast/netanyahu-israel-elections-arabs.html&quot;&gt;against Israeli Arab voters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; on Tuesday showed that he has forfeited any claim to representing all Israelis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The professional self-flagellator, Bradley Burston of Haaretz kept it going with &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haaretz.com/blogs/a-special-place-in-hell/.premium-1.647564&quot;&gt;As an Israeli, I am ashamed that my prime minister is a racist&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am ashamed to know that the prime minister of Israel is either a racist, which is a horrible thought, or that he incites racism in others for the sake of votes - which is worse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jeffrey Goldberg or the Atlantic joined the chorus with &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2015/03/bibi-deploys-the-southern-strategy/388096/&quot;&gt;Bibi Deploys the Southern Strategy&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;quot; who, after celebrating Israel&amp;#39;s diverse democracy, including the fact that the Supreme Court Justice in charge of elections is, in fact, an Israeli Arab, charges that Netanyahu is the Israeli Lee Atwater:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Netanyahu, of course, wasn&amp;#39;t dog-whistling here: He didn&amp;#39;t refer, say, to &amp;quot;people in Israel&amp;#39;s north who don&amp;#39;t have Jewish interests at heart,&amp;quot; or some other such variation (Paul Ryan&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;urban&amp;quot; voter formulation from 2012 comes to mind). Instead, &lt;strong&gt;he screamed, &amp;#39;The Arabs are coming!&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are all serious allegations: &lt;em&gt;If the Prime Minister is a racist and just won another victory by appealing to racism, surely Israel and most Israelis are racists as well!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Judean People&amp;#39;s Front and its followers know this to be false, so let&amp;#39;s look at what Netanyahu actually said:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;The rule of the Right is in danger. The Arab voters are moving in droves toward the polling places. The NGOs of the Left are bringing them in buses.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This sounds bad to Western ears who aren&amp;#39;t used to mainstream leaders referring to communities by their names. But in Israel this is par for the course. Talking about Arabs, not to mention seculars, Haredim, national-religious, settlers, Mizrahim, etc. is simply the way things are and there is nothing inherently wrong with that. Multiculturalists love the idea of different cultures but hate talking about them, and always condemn someone who is part of the majority culture for expressing pride in their culture or discussing a different group in any terms that aren&amp;#39;t flattering or welcoming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some have asked, &amp;quot;what if Odeh complained that Jews were coming out to vote in droves?&amp;quot; Well, this analogy doesn&amp;#39;t really work because Israeli Jews are divided among various, sometimes-fluid groups. When &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesofisrael.com/prominent-rabbi-skips-vote-boding-ill-for-ultra-orthodox-parties/&quot;&gt;Rabbi Auerbach effectively called for a boycott of the elections&lt;/a&gt; there was much discussion of how this would effect the Haredi vote... and the New York Times certainly didn&amp;#39;t label these discussions anti-Haredi or anti-Semitic. It was understandable and reasonable to discuss how the Haredi sector was going to vote. So why should it be any different when discussing the Arab vote? (Granted, the Arab sector is also sub-divided into many groups - Bedouin, Islamist, communist, Palestinian Nationalist, Christian - but the Joint List shows that most of these groups will abandon or suppress their differeneces in order to rally around anti-Zionism.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another thing completely overlooked is the make-up of the Joint Arab List, which sounds all nice and cozy. Again from the NYTimes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were signs that Arab Israelis were turning out in somewhat higher numbers, apparently to vote for the Joint Arab List, a coalition of four small parties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the only line devoted to Arab actions as opposed to the actions of Jews. The Arabs are again only the victims of a racist Israeli leadership and society. The Times Editorial Board was too busy to look into what the JAL stands for, but the &lt;a href=&quot;judeanpf.com/2015/03/15/Why-Arab-Parties-are-never-in-governing-coalitions/&quot;&gt;Judean People&amp;#39;s Front found the time&lt;/a&gt;. So let&amp;#39;s do a quick recap of the leadership shall we?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Number 1: Ayman Odeh&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the Communist, anti-Zionist Hadash party. He calls for Israel to cease being a Jewish State, while calling for a Palestinian Arab State to be created next to it (until they can be merged, one must assume).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Number 2: Masud Ghnaim&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the Islamic Movement and Ra&amp;#39;am party. He calls for Israel to be replaced with a Caliphate and openly supports Iran and Hezbollah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Number 3: Jamal Zahalaka&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the Palestinian Nationalist Balad party. He travels the world calling Israel an apartheid state that should be replaced by a &amp;quot;state for all its citizens,&amp;quot; which is code for a Palestinian dominated state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Number 4: Ahmad Tibi&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the anti-Zionist Ta&amp;#39;al party. When he isn&amp;#39;t supporting dictators like the late Muammar Ghadafi, Bashar al-Assad, or Mahmoud Abbas, Tibi is promoting Fatah, being celebrated by Hamas for representing Palestinians and is calling for Israel to cease being Jewish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Herein lies the problem: it isn&amp;#39;t that Arabs in Israel are voting for Arab parties; that is their right and given Israel&amp;#39;s fractious political system, it is to be expected. The problem is that the Arabs overwhelmingly are voting for a ticket that is diametrically opposed to the character of the state. Bradley Burston complains of the division between Zionists and the anti-Zionists, but he of course charges that only Bibi gets to decide who belongs in which group. Instead of actually looking at the fact that the Arab community in Israel actually does vote for proud and open anti-Zionists (not simply left wingers derogatorily labeled as such), Burston sticks to what he does best: ignoring the facts and calling his opponents racist. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Martin Luther King vs. Malcolm X&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/a4s3QO4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;MLK v MX&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the Civil Rights Movement in the United States, there were two main groups fighting for leadership: the Integrationists, led by Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. and the Black Nationalists, led by Malcolm X.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their differences were stark: Dr. King was working toward a realization of the civil rights promised all citizens under the US Constitution and a full integration of African American citizens into the state. Conversely, Malcolm X preached separation between Black and While people, black supremacy, and the creation of an independent black nation in the American South.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine for a moment if the African American community had for generations referred to anyone who worked with the American political system not only as an Uncle Tom, but a traitor worthy of death (and often carried out such sentences). In such a scenario, it is unlikely Martin Luther King Jr. would have been able to found a movement, let alone gain followers in public. That would have ceded the stage to the separatist Black Nationalism of Malcolm X. The militant, separatist, and anti-American nature of this movement would have completely overshadowed the legitimate concerns about discrimination and segregation of the African American community. White Americans would not have felt comfortable supporting such a movement and such support would have been rejected anyway. The March on Washington would have been about destruction not dreams. There would have been no Civil Rights Amendment, no end to segregation, and instead there would have been a radical polarization in America, most likely leading to a race war as Black Nationalists attempted secession.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If African Americans were by a wide margin voting only for the Communist Workers Party or the Nation of Islam, would anyone blame the rest of the country for being wary of them?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Luckily for America, Dr. King&amp;#39;s message of civil rights, equality, and integration won the day, making him a true American leader and not only an African American leader. Unluckily for Israel&amp;#39;s Arabs (who face no such segregation or official discrimination) the ideology of Malcolm X has gone largely unchallenged. Instead of rallying around people like Bassem Eid or Khaled Abu Toameh, they rally around the Joint Arab List, a coalition of parties whose only unifying factor is their opposition to the State of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pointing out the radical, anti-Zionist nature of the Joint Arab List is not racist and unless this fact is seriously discussed, the danger it poses to both Israel its Arab citizens will only grow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Room for Hope?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is another aspect to this that deserves attention: &lt;a href=&quot;http://evelyncgordon.com/the-half-full-cup-of-jewish-arab-relations/&quot;&gt;recent polls show&lt;/a&gt; that not only has Arab identification with the Israeli flag (and possibly the state it represents?) jumped to 55% (from 37% last year), but Israeli Arab support for the Palestinian flag plummetted from 34% down to a mere 8%. Additionally, 87% of Israeli Arabs say they believe in &amp;quot;Jewish-Arab coexistence,&amp;quot; though that is conveniently left undefined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is also worth noting that Israeli Arabs turned out to vote in higher percentages than the national average (70% vs. 66%), clearly showing they believe the current system is a legitimate way to redress their grievances. 70% of Arabs in Israel say they care more about socio-economic issues within Israel than the conflict with the Palestinians, and 60% say they want the Joint List in the coalition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This begs the question: If 81% of Israeli Arabs say that better integration can only come with Arabs in the coalition and 55% support the state, then why on Earth are they voting for the Arab List? Why aren&amp;#39;t new Israeli Arab parties being founded that are not anti-Zionist?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, periodically you will hear about such parties being formed, but nothing ever comes of them for a number of reasons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;It costs money to get elected&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Incumbency matters&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;All parties must get at least 3.25% of the total vote and such parties would be campaigning mostly for the Arab votes which are only 20% of the country&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fear of being labeled a traitor&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first three reasons are all just excuses that are surmountable under the right circumstances. Pretty much every Israeli election these days has a new party crashing onto the scene. I don&amp;#39;t accept that if someone like an &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Amos_Yarkoni&quot;&gt;Amos Yarkoni&lt;/a&gt; established a pro-Israel party for Arabs he couldn&amp;#39;t get funding or challenge the established parties and pass the threshold.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The real question is, despite the growing identification with the state, are Arabs in Israel willing to make this public by going to a rally for such a party instead of just answering questions in a poll? So far the answer is no, although to be fair, none of the new parties have offered the kind of leadership or charisma (real or imagined) of a Lapid or Kahlon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The polls showing greater Arab identification with Israel are certainly promising, but as long as threats continue to dictate public actions and anti-Zionists continue to win the votes, those feelings of affinity are meaningless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/18/The-Arabs-are-Voting/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/18/The-Arabs-are-Voting/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Arab MK Posters</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/15/Why-Arab-Parties-are-never-in-governing-coalitions/&quot;&gt;Our last post&lt;/a&gt; went into detail about the extremist positions of the MKs running on the Joint Arab List ticket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But given that visuals are often more effective than well thought out arguments and blocks of text, we&amp;#39;ve put together some handy posters for use on social media.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please help us make these spread!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Ayman Odeh&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/UhbfHit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Odeh&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Masud Ganaim&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/W4Pkqax.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ganaim&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Jamal Zahalaka&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/d1MAv9z.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Zahalaka&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Ahmad Tibi&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/LBXbiim.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tibi&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Hanin Zoabi&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/65wkgzp.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Zoabi&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Raja Zaatra&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/tc7MbPo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Zaatra&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/16/Arab-MK-Posters/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/16/Arab-MK-Posters/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Why Arab parties are never in governing coalitions</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;h3&gt;And why that isn&amp;#39;t likely to change any time soon.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our &lt;a href=&quot;http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/11/No-Labor-is-not-on-the-road-to-victory/&quot;&gt;post the other day&lt;/a&gt;, we dangerously waded into the current election and predicted that even though it is probable that Labor will win more seats than Likud, since the Right-wing/religious parties will have more seats overall, Netanyahu is more likely form the next government. (We still think this is most likely, but pollsters have had a difficult time getting the numbers for the small parties right recently, we could be in for a disappointment ourselves. Time will tell.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the reasons we gave was that the Joint Arab list has said &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesofisrael.com/no-matter-how-left-wing-arab-parties-wont-join-coalition/&quot;&gt;it will not join a coalition&lt;/a&gt;, with party leader Ayman Odeh even saying &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesofisrael.com/after-uniting-arabs-behind-him-ayman-odeh-looks-to-lead-opposition/&quot;&gt;he wants to lead the opposition&lt;/a&gt;. “I believe that whether Herzog or Netanyahu are tasked with forming the government, they will both head to a national unity cabinet. That means we will lead the opposition, which is an extremely important podium.” he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The current polls give the Joint Arab list a strong chance to be the third-largest party in the Knesset (albeit with only 13 or so seats), which under normal circumstances would give that party a good opportunity to get the position Odeh desires. But this just simply is not going to happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason why Odeh will not lead the opposition is not because he is Arab, though that is certainly the reason given by many Arabs and the anti-Israel crowd. &lt;strong&gt;The real reason why Odeh or any other member of the Arab parties currently in the Joint List will never head the opposition is because they are not Zionist&lt;/strong&gt;. It will come as no surprise to the followers of this blog that the Judean People&amp;#39;s Front is no fan of the Left-wing parties in Israel, but as much as we disagree with them, we recognize that they are still Zionist parties (however misguided they may be).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem has always been that while Arabs do often vote for and are elected as members of mainstream Zionist parties, parties catering specifically to the Arab sector have always been non or anti-Zionist, run by communists, Islamists, and/or traitors who openly side with the enemy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(For JPF&amp;#39;s posters about the Arab MKs &lt;a href=&quot;http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/16/Arab-MK-Posters/&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The Arab Parties&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s take a quick look at the ideologies of these parties from Wikipedia:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hadash&quot;&gt;Hadash&lt;/a&gt; (the only joint Arab-Jewish party):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hadash defines itself as a non-Zionist party&lt;/strong&gt;, originally in keeping with Marxist opposition to nationalism. It calls for recognition of Palestinian Arabs as a national minority within Israel. &lt;strong&gt;Hadash shifted to a more Arab nationalist appeal&lt;/strong&gt; after running on a joint list with Ta&amp;#39;al in 2003. Avirama Golan of Haaretz wrote in 2007 that &lt;strong&gt;Hadash had &amp;quot;succumbed to the separatist-nationalist and populist stream&lt;/strong&gt;...&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Balad_(political_party)&quot;&gt;Balad&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Balad is a political party whose stated purpose is the &lt;strong&gt;&amp;quot;struggle to transform the state of Israel into a democracy for all its citizens&lt;/strong&gt;, irrespective of national or ethnic identity&amp;quot;. &lt;strong&gt;It opposes the idea of Israel as a solely Jewish state, and supports its recasting as a binational state.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Arab_List&quot;&gt;Raam&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its constituency consists mostly of religious or nationalist Israeli Arabs, and enjoys particular popularity among the Bedouin... &lt;strong&gt;The southern faction of the Islamic Movement is now the dominant force in the party&lt;/strong&gt;, whilst other factions include the Arab National Party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ahmad_Tibi&quot;&gt;Ta&amp;#39;al run by Ahmed Tibi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tibi is an Anti-Zionist&lt;/strong&gt;. He supports an Israeli withdrawal to the pre-1967 borders and a two-state solution, with a Palestinian state established alongside Israel. &lt;strong&gt;He also opposes Israel&amp;#39;s character as a Jewish state, claiming that its self-definition as Jewish is racist&lt;/strong&gt;, and favors Israel becoming a &amp;quot;state of all its citizens&amp;quot;. Accordingly, he supports removing icons that represent the special status of the Jewish majority, including theLaw of Return, the flag, and the national anthem. He opposes the recruitment of Israeli-Arabs into the IDF. Tibi also supports the Palestinian right of return, calling it a prerequisite for reconciliation, but has stated that he believes only a small percentage of Palestinian refugees would actually choose to move to Israel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video-container&quot;&gt;
         &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ewhDBWZF688?feature=player_embedded&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The Arab Leaders&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now some more info about those running these parties:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Balad used to be run by &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Azmi_Bishara#Resignation_from_Knesset&quot;&gt;Azmi Bishara&lt;/a&gt;, until he resigned in 2007 while under investigation for passing sensitive information to Hezbollah during the Second Lebanon War of 2006. While this was shocking, considering that he traveled to Syria in 2001 to give a speech in support of Assad and Hezbollah, it probably shouldn&amp;#39;t have. Since then, Balad has been run by &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jamal_Zahalka#Views_on_the_treatment_of_Palestinians_by_Israel&quot;&gt;Jamal Zahalaka&lt;/a&gt; who publicly calls Israel an apartheid state. &lt;em&gt;Remember all those black members of the South African parliament who openly spoke against their government without fear? What? They didn&amp;#39;t exist because apartheid systems don&amp;#39;t allow for the disadvantaged group to serve or speak freely? Interesting.&lt;/em&gt; Zahalaka is of course joined by the famous &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Haneen_Zoabi&quot;&gt;Hanin Zoabi&lt;/a&gt; who participated in the IHH attempt to break through the legal naval blockade of Gaza and last summer publicly said the murderers of Naftali, Gil-ad, and Eyal were not terrorists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hadash used to be run by &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mohammad_Barakeh#Indictment&quot;&gt;Mohammad Barakeh&lt;/a&gt; who in 2009 was &amp;quot;indicted on four counts for actions taken at political demonstrations.&amp;quot; It is now headed by &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ayman_Odeh&quot;&gt;Ayman Odeh&lt;/a&gt; who also heads the Joint List ticket. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesofisrael.com/after-uniting-arabs-behind-him-ayman-odeh-looks-to-lead-opposition/&quot;&gt;The most covered statement&lt;/a&gt; he has made during this campaign has centered around his alleged acceptance of Israel as the Jewish state:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe that the Jewish people have a right to self-determination, which the State of Israel has fulfilled. The Palestinian state is meant to realize the right to self-determination of the Arab Palestinian people, and here it ends. In other words, the fact that Jews in Israel enjoy the right to self-determination doesn’t mean they should discriminate against the Arabs. I certainly won’t agree that in my homeland — which is today a joint homeland for both our peoples — the state will be defined and effectively act as the state of only one nation. I want to see myself everywhere and be a full partner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;There&amp;#39;s a lot in there, so let&amp;#39;s unpack it a little.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First he states that he believes Israel fulfilled the legitimate right to self-determination by the Jews. &lt;em&gt;Sounds good to us.&lt;/em&gt; The he says that a future Palestinian state should do the same for the Palestinians. &lt;em&gt;Again, makes sense (if a state were to ever exist peacefully).&lt;/em&gt; He continues that Jews in Israel shouldn&amp;#39;t discriminate against Arabs. &lt;em&gt;No arguments here, though we would remind him that discrimination across the board is far worse in every single Arab country.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, his acceptance of Jewish self-determination is then undone when he says that he is against the state being defined &amp;quot;as the state of only one nation.&amp;quot; He advocates establishing a Palestinian state in which Palestinian Arab nationalism will be the sole nationality, but insists that Israel become a binational state. He does not want to be a &amp;quot;full partner.&amp;quot; &lt;strong&gt;He wants to undermine the foundation of the State of Israel and fundamentally alter its makeup&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is Odeh&amp;#39;s Hadash party that sent &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.co/bXQMbUS10e&quot;&gt;Raja Zaatra&lt;/a&gt;, a member of the party&amp;#39;s secretariat and a PR official, to a panel discussion at Bar Ilan University, where he said, &amp;quot;Where did ISIS (Islamic State) learn all these things? Look at what the Zionist movement did in 1948, the acts of rape, murder, plunder, and mass slaughter that were committed.” In response, the Joint List, instead of condemning the remarks and firing Zaatra, quickly issued an order to its members to refrain from controversial remarks that would hurt them at the polls. It also said, &amp;quot;The remarks were made in response to a provocation by one of the panel’s participants, who claimed that ISIS learned its actions from the Joint List.&amp;quot; Such &amp;quot;provocations,&amp;quot; if they indeed happened, might have been somewhat hyperbolic, but given that the Joint List includes Islamists like &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ibrahim_Sarsur#Controversies&quot;&gt;Ibrahim Sarsur&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Masud_Ghnaim&quot;&gt;Masud Ghnaim&lt;/a&gt; of Ra&amp;#39;am - who have not only compared Israel to Nazi Germany and openly praised Hezbollah and Iran, but actually &lt;strong&gt;called for the establishment of a Caliphate in place of Israel&lt;/strong&gt; - it isn&amp;#39;t totally off-base. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So let&amp;#39;s review the components of the Joint Arab List, shall we? It consists of communists who would replace democracy, anti-Zionists seeking to undo the Jewish character of the Jewish State, Islamists who want to replace Israel with a Caliphate, and supporters of terrorism and enemy dictatorships. Do these sound like people you would expect to be in an Israeli governing coalition? Do these sound like people who you would expect to even be allowed to serve in the Israeli parliament? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They aren&amp;#39;t being marginalized because they are Arab, they are being marginalized because they are extremists!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Is this even legal?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is even more astounding when we examine &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mfa.gov.il/mfa/mfa-archive/1950-1959/pages/basic%20law-%20the%20knesset%20-1958-%20-%20updated%20translatio.aspx&quot;&gt;Basic Law: The Knesset&lt;/a&gt;. Most democracies have restrictions on what are and are not acceptable political parties, with strictures varying from country to country. Israel&amp;#39;s Basic Law discusses this in Section 7A &amp;quot;Prevention of participation of candidates list:&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A candidates list shall not participate in elections to the Knesset, and a person shall not be a candidate for election to the Knesset, if the goals or actions of the list or the actions of the person, expressly or by implication, include one of the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(1) negation of the existence of the State of Israel as a Jewish and democratic state;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(2) incitement to racism;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(3) support for armed struggle by a hostile state or a terrorist organization against the State of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are these unreasonable demands? Acceptance of democracy and the Jewish character of Israel, rejecting racism, not supporting violence against the state; I find it hard to believe anyone would say these are overly restrictive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But these very lax guidelines have been violated by every single one of the parties making up the Joint Arab List! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Supreme Court has overturned every single attempt to disqualify an Arab party or MK from running, ostensibly because the actions haven&amp;#39;t been proven sufficiently (a ridiculous excuse in most cases) but in truth because they don&amp;#39;t want to disqualify Arabs from running regardless of their offenses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only parties ever successfully banned from running for the Knesset were &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kach_and_Kahane_Chai&quot;&gt;Kach and Kahane Chai&lt;/a&gt; and were subsequently banned outright after being reclassified as terrorist organizations. If you look at the actions and statements made by these groups, I trust you&amp;#39;re happy they were banned for their racism and threats to democracy. However, the statements and actions of many of the current members of the Arab parties are just as bad, if not worse and yet they are allowed to continue to run, serve, and gain parliamentary immunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only is this in itself racist, as it holds Jews and Arabs to different standards, but it is incredibly destructive to the Arab community in Israel. Currently, Israeli Arabs overwhelmingly vote for the Arab parties available, but if these extremists were banned, it might be possible for a party to form and gain votes that actually cares about the Arab citizens of Israel. Such a party could join a governing coalition (even if it asks for a clause exempting it from voting in favor of military operations). But instead, Arabs continue to vote for extremists who will never join a government or actually work to better their own communities and instead fan the flames of extremism, making it more difficult for Arabs to integrate into Israeli society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Freedom of Expression vs. Extremism&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, the Judean People’s Front is conflicted about this law: should the government decide who can and can’t run in elections? Is it better to force extremists underground or allow them to stay public? In debates about citizens’ freedoms, we are inclined to lean towards more freedom and allow extremists the right to run and lose in elections. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, if the law exists, it must be applied equally across the board. If Jewish extremists are going to be banned from running, so should Arab extremists. If the Supreme Court believes extremists should still be able to run, then it should rule Section 7 of Basic Law: Knesset to be unconstitutional. But until this is done, extremists of all stripes must be treated equally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until Israel’s Arabs get a party that is more interested in bettering the lives of its community than it is in extremism, there will never be an Arab party in the coalition. This is both detrimental to the Arabs themselves who will lack true leadership and to the rest of the State of Israel that will continue to lose the potential of 20% of its citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We would be wise to remember the words of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ze%27ev_Jabotinsky#Integrated_state_with_Arabs&quot;&gt;Ze’ev Jabotinsky&lt;/a&gt; who said, &amp;quot;in every cabinet where the prime minister is a Jew, the vice-premiership shall be offered to an Arab and vice versa.&amp;quot; But as long as the only Arabs in government are extremists, communists, and Islamists, this vision will go unrealized and we all shall suffer the consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/15/Why-Arab-Parties-are-never-in-governing-coalitions/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/15/Why-Arab-Parties-are-never-in-governing-coalitions/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>No, Labor is not on the road to victory</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;It is impossible to go on an Israeli news site today and not see the headlines touting a purported Labor, sorry, I mean &lt;em&gt;Zionist Union&lt;/em&gt;, victory in the upcoming elections. You can hear the shouts of excitement coming from the bubbles of Tel Aviv, but these will soon be replaced with cries of disappointment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is not to say that Labor will not get more votes than Likud. It very well might and most polls now put it 3-4 seats ahead. But given Israel&amp;#39;s parliamentary system, this is almost entirely irrelevant. It isn&amp;#39;t enough for one party to merely get more seats because in the end they will need to build a coalition of 60 + 1 members in order to govern and the parties of the Left just don&amp;#39;t have the numbers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s look at the two most recent polls - &lt;a href=&quot;http://knessetjeremy.com/2015/03/11/midgamarmy-radio-poll-zionist-union-24-likud-21-bayit-yehudi-13-yesh-atid-12-the-joint-arab-list-12-kulanu-8/&quot;&gt;Midgam/Army Radio Poll&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://knessetjeremy.com/2015/03/11/midgamchannel-2-poll-zionist-union-25-likud-21-bayit-yehudi-13-the-joint-arab-list-13-yesh-atid-12-kulanu-8/&quot;&gt;Midgam/Channel 2 Poll&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Current Knesset seats in [brackets]&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;24-25 [20] Zionist Union (Labor-Livni)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;21 [18] Likud&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13 [11] Bayit Yehudi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12-13 [20] Yesh Atid&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12-13 [11] The Joint (Arab) List&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;08 [02] Kulanu (Kahlon+Kadima)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;07 [10] Shas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;06-07 [07] Yahadut Hatorah/UTJ&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;06 [13] Yisrael Beitenu&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;05-06 [06] Meretz&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;04 [02] Yachad (Yishai+Chetboun+Marzel)
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
65-66 [63] Right-Religious-Kahlon (Parties that have not ruled out nominating Netanyahu in Phase 2)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;55-54 [57] Center-Left-Arab (Parties that have ruled out nominating Netanyahu in Phase 2)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is possible that Kulanu could join a Leftist government (his socialist economic agenda is pretty leftist as it is, and he has made it clear he wants the Finance Ministry). But since the Joint Arab List has said &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesofisrael.com/no-matter-how-left-wing-arab-parties-wont-join-coalition/&quot;&gt;it will not join a coalition&lt;/a&gt;, even with Kahlon, the Left is still 11-12 seats shy of a majority.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s say the Left tries to bring in the Ultra-Orthodox parties (excluding Yachad with Baruch Marzel). This would force Meretz out of the coalition and only net a total of 57-60 seats. This would also pose a problem for Yesh Atid as it would also not want to be in such a coalition and Deri is unlikely to agree to join one with Lapid either. So while a few seats might swing a majority here, it&amp;#39;s still a longshot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, it is unlikely the Ultra-Orthodox and Kulanu voters would even want to be part of a Leftist government (though at that point they would no longer have a say in the matter) since 68% of Kulanu voters identify as Right or Center-Right, as well as 69% of Shas voters, and 79% of UTJ voters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some have floated the idea of the Joint Arab List supporting a minority government from outside the coalition as the Arab parties did for Rabin during Oslo. But this fails to take into account the incredibly different times we live in over 20 years later. Back then much of Israel was willing to take the risk of supporting Rabin with Oslo, but today, the opposite is true:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.idi.org.il/media/3930815/Peace_Index_February_2015-Eng.pdf&quot;&gt;Israel Democracy Institute&amp;#39;s most recent Peace Index Poll&lt;/a&gt;-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a clear majority (63.5%) strongly or moderately agrees with the claim that “No matter which party forms the next government, the peace process with the Palestinians will not advance because there is no solution to the disagreements between the sides.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only thing surprising here is that this number isn&amp;#39;t higher. There is no viable solution to our problems with the Palestinians because they refuse any and all reasonable offers made to them, insist on the &amp;quot;Right of Return&amp;quot; which would destroy Israel&amp;#39;s Jewish character, and continue to finance terrorists who kill Jews. In short, their goal has been, and remains, the destruction of the Jewish State.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Likud Has a Much Easier Path to a Coalition&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But let&amp;#39;s say that the election is even closer, Labor gets more seats than Likud and is tapped to have the first shot at forming a coalition. Not only would this be incredibly difficult on its own, but Likud will also send out messages to its natural allies in the Right, Center-Right, and religious parties, indicating what a Likud-led government would look like. Netanyahu would likely be able to form a coalition even without the Ultra-Orthodox, or include them all, or play Yachad against Shas to get a solid majority without giving up too much. The point is Netanyahu has many roads to a coalition and all of them are more likely and easier to muster than anything Herzog-Livni can muster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upsets are always possible and roughly 7% of voters are still undecided (14% if you include those who are deciding between 2 parties on the same political spectrum), so I&amp;#39;ve always been wary of predictions. But it is hard to look at the data and the trends and not draw the clear conclusions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is it possible Labor will cobble together a weak coalition and eek out a victory? Sure. It just isn&amp;#39;t very likely&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now let&amp;#39;s just hope Netanyahu can easily and quickly put together a new coalition and get back to work. So remember to vote on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/11/No-Labor-is-not-on-the-road-to-victory/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/11/No-Labor-is-not-on-the-road-to-victory/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>The Many Myths of Jerusalem: Part 1</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Given the penchant for myth-making in the Middle East, it is no surprise that many legends have popped up around the Holy City of Jerusalem. Unfortunately, given the pervasive nature of these myths, most people don&amp;#39;t even recognize them as such.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we here at the Judean People&amp;#39;s Front, having long since abandoned &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NUHk2RSMCS8&quot;&gt;our suicide squads&lt;/a&gt; have instead decided to fight back by exposing these myths for what they are: lies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This begins our multipart series on &lt;strong&gt;The Many Myths of Jerusalem&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Myth Number 1: Jerusalem Must be Internationalized&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most people probably think the current borders of Jerusalem are a result of the Jordanian occupation of the eastern part of the city in 1948 that led to the city&amp;#39;s division for 19 years. However, this was only a partial cause. The true source of this actually stems from Jordan&amp;#39;s sponsor at the time: Great Britain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After 27 years of unsuccessfully ruling its Mandate of Palestine, the British resolved to abandon the territory, recommending it be divided between the Jews and Arabs, with the Arab section to be joined with Jordan (then known as Transjordan or East Jordan in Arabic). In dividing the territory, it only made sense for areas with a Jewish majority to go to the Zionists, and areas with an Arab majority to go to the Arabs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this brought up a major problem: since &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jerusalem#1917.E2.80.931948_.E2.88.92_British_Mandate&quot;&gt;Jerusalem was two-thirds Jewish&lt;/a&gt; (with over 100,000 Jews, 1/6th of Israel&amp;#39;s population at the time) that would require handing the holy city over to Israel. That simply would not work for the British, so they had to find a workaround.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After putting together all the heads in Perfidious Albion, the Brits finally came up with a solution:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If Jerusalem has a Jewish majority within its current borders, let&amp;#39;s just redraw the borders until &amp;quot;Jerusalem&amp;quot; has more Arabs than Jews!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From &lt;a href=&quot;http://domino.un.org/unispal.nsf/0/7f0af2bd897689b785256c330061d253&quot;&gt;UNGA Resolution 181 (II)&lt;/a&gt; Part III, Section B:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The City of Jerusalem shall include the present municipality of Jerusalem &lt;strong&gt;plus the surrounding villages and towns&lt;/strong&gt;, the most eastern of which shall be Abu Dis; the most southern, Bethlehem; the most western, Ein Karim (including also the built-up area of Motsa); and the most northern Shu&amp;#39;fat, as indicated on the attached sketch-map (&lt;a href=&quot;http://domino.un.org/unispal.nsf/5ba47a5c6cef541b802563e000493b8c/3f1bd9477022a0c285256cc500530c1f?OpenDocument&quot;&gt;annex B&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Guess what happens when a number of Arab towns, villages, and even a whole city, none of which have ever been considered part of Jerusalem, with a combined population of over 40,000, is added to the municipality? Surprise, surprise, Jerusalem all of a sudden has a slight Arab majority for the first time in over 100 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/3LNMDOD.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Corpus Separatum&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(The above map is from the &amp;quot;Palestinian Academic Society for the Study of International Affairs.&amp;quot; It quotes Section A of Part III if UNGAR 181, but noticeably ignores Section B where the expansion of the city is discussed.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that the British had manipulated the situation to make it seem as though Jerusalem had an Arab majority, they needed to make the disconnect between the city and Israel permanent. So they added Section D to Part III announcing that after ten years, should the Trusteeship Council agree, the &amp;quot;residents of the City&amp;quot; could vote in a referendum &amp;quot;their wishes as to possible modifications of the regime of the City&amp;quot; such as adding it to the Arab state. In this way, the British were hoping to make sure that Jerusalem would never fall under Jewish control since the new Jewish minority would be unable to vote for unification with Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since UNGAR 181 takes the expanded borders as a fait accompli, it refers to the Corpus Separatum simply as the &amp;quot;City of Jerusalem.&amp;quot; Unless you were to actually read this single paragraph of 53 words, you&amp;#39;d never know there was a change at all. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Had the Arabs accepted UNGAR 181 (as Israel did) Israel would have lost the entire city of Jerusalem from the start. However we all know the Arabs did not accept partition - the second in a long line of peace deals they have rejected - and their ensuing attack allowed Israel to retaliate and retain the western half of the city. Unfortunately, this also meant the eastern half was conquered by Jordan, which subsequently desecrated and destroyed anything that looked remotely Jewish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Renewed Calls for Internationalization&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, there are once more calls from the radical fringes to internationalize Jerusalem. Of course, after 1950, there were no such entreaties (how interesting!), which would have entailed removing Jordanian and, therefore, Muslim control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might be thinking &amp;quot;sure, but this is only suggested by radicals,&amp;quot; and that is true... for now. But radical ideas can become mainstream when not properly understood or countered by rational and factual arguments. This radical idea also has the added advantage of still being the official position of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Corpus_separatum_(Jerusalem)#International_support&quot;&gt;UN, EU, US, and Vatican&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to ensure the international community does not accept such an extreme position, it is important to recognize that just as the first drive for internationalization was attempted against the wishes of the majority population through tricks of demographics and border modifications, and the same is true today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also is interesting that although it is currently quite fashionable to rail against the colonial pasts of the British and French empires and their drawing of borders throughout the Middle East without regard for the wishes of the local populations, when it comes to Jerusalem, these same people wish to reestablish just such a border.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess colonialism is only ok when it is to the detriment of the Jews and not the Arabs. Go figure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/10/Jerusalem-Myth-01/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/10/Jerusalem-Myth-01/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Just One Question for FM Zarif</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;h3&gt;About that Cyrus guy you mentioned...&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After Prime Minister Netanyahu&amp;#39;s &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/post-politics/wp/2015/03/03/full-text-netanyahus-address-to-congress/&quot;&gt;masterful speech to Congress&lt;/a&gt; last week, in which he clearly laid out why the current deal being offered is so dangerous in light of continued Iranian aggression and terror around the world, Iranian Foreign Minister Mohammad Javad Zarif sat down with MSNBC&amp;#39;s Ann Curry to respond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since Zarif has had so much experience duping American nuclear negotiators, the fact that he is able to do so easily to a reporter should be of no surprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;IMG SRC=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/FRx9RCv.jpg&quot; ALT=&quot;some text&quot; WIDTH=700 HEIGHT=500&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But still, Curry does of decent job holding Zarif&amp;#39;s feet to the fire, asking him specifically &amp;quot;Netanyahu strongly suggested that Iran has genocidal ambitions against the Jewish people, saying, &amp;quot;Iran&amp;#39;s regime is not merely a Jewish problem, any more than the Nazis were a Jewish problem.&amp;quot; What is your response to that?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to counter this question that deserves a real answer from the Iranian negotiating team, Zarif digs deep into history saying:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, it is unfortunate that Mr. Netanyahu now totally-- distorts realities of today. He even distorts his own scripture. &lt;strong&gt;If you read the Book of Esther, you will see that it was the Iranian king who saved the Jews. If you read the Old Testament, you will see that it was an Iranian king who saved the Jews from Babylon.&lt;/strong&gt; Esther has a town in Iran where-- where our Jewish population, &lt;strong&gt;which is the largest in the Middle East&lt;/strong&gt;-- visit on a regular basis. It is-- it is truly, truly regrettable that bigotry gets to the point of making allegations against an entire nation which has saved Jews three times in its history: Once during that time of a prime minister who was trying to kill the Jews, and the king saved the Jews, again during the time of Cyrus the Great, where he saved the Jews from Babylon, and &lt;strong&gt;during the Second World War, where Iran saved the Jews&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I applaud the Foreign Minister&amp;#39;s verbal and historical acrobatics, but it would have been nice if Curry challenged him on any of the many above inaccuracies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Ignoring Queen Esther&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.vox.com/2015/3/5/8157079/zarif-netanyahu-esther&quot;&gt;Vox.com&lt;/a&gt; called Zarif out for misrepresenting the story of Queen Esther. Yes it was King Achashverosh/Xerxes who &amp;quot;saved the Jews from a Prime Minister,&amp;quot; but it was the same king who had previously signed off on their annihilation and only countered the decree after the intervention of his Jewish bride.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Did the Holocaust Happen or Not?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zarif&amp;#39;s mention of Iranian efforts to save Jews during WWII was no doubt a reference to &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Abdol_Hossein_Sardari&quot;&gt;Abdol Hossein Sardari&lt;/a&gt; who did in fact issue hundreds of Iranian passports to Jews (both Iranian and non-Iranian) and is often called the &amp;quot;Schindler of Iran.&amp;quot; Given the Islamic Republic&amp;#39;s history of Holocaust Denial, it is interesting that Zarif would mention this at all. But of course he doesn&amp;#39;t talk about the fact that after the Islamic Revolution, instead of supporting such a worthy humanitarian, the new Islamist government rescinded his pension and confiscated his property. It must have been this &amp;quot;generous&amp;quot; policy towards those who worked to save Jews that convinced more than 90% of Iran&amp;#39;s Jews they would be better off emigrating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Iranian Jews&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He also says that Iran has the &amp;quot;largest [Jewish population] in the Middle East.&amp;quot; This is nonsense. Israel has the largest Jewish population in the Middle East, followed by Turkey. If Iran actually had 20,000 Jews, as Zarif claims, it would have more than Turkey&amp;#39;s 17,000, but a &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Persian_Jews#Islamic_Republic_.281979.E2.80.93present.29&quot;&gt;2012 census&lt;/a&gt; at less than 9,000. But Iran&amp;#39;s Jews are routinely trotted out by the government to &lt;a href=&quot;judeanpf.com/2015/03/02/blue-and-whitewashing/&quot;&gt;Blue-and-Whitewash&lt;/a&gt; away its anti-Semitism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Back to that Cyrus guy you mentioned...&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I think the most important question that should have been asked in response, was about Zarif&amp;#39;s characterization of the actions of Cyrus the Great, who he describes as &amp;quot;saving the Jews from Babylon.&amp;quot; This is certainly true. However, what Zarif fails to mention is that in freeing the Jews exiled to Babylon, &lt;strong&gt;he allowed them to return to Israel and ordered them to rebuild the Temple in Jerusalem.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;IMG SRC=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2e/Illustrerad_Verldshistoria_band_I_Ill_058.jpg&quot; ALT=&quot;some text&quot; WIDTH=500 HEIGHT=725&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon hearing Zarif talk about King Cyrus the Great, how is the next question not: Do you recognize the established history that states that Cyrus not only liberated the exiled Jews in Babylon, but instructed them to return to the Land of Israel and rebuild the Temple in Jerusalem? Do you deny this undisputed fact of history, showing the Jewish connection and right to the Land of Israel that was also recognized by the great Iranian King Cyrus?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cyrus&amp;#39;s role in reestablishing Jewish life in Israel and rebuilding the Temple is not questioned by any historian. In fact, in 1953, when visiting the Jewish Theological Seminary, President Truman&amp;#39;s Eddie Jacobson introduced him as “the man who helped create the state of Israel.” To which Truman responded, “What do you mean ‘helped to create’? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.newrepublic.com/article/116215/was-harry-truman-zionist&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I am Cyrus&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/a&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;IMG SRC=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/x3ssRMu.jpg&quot; ALT=&quot;some text&quot; WIDTH=566 HEIGHT=721&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course Zarif can&amp;#39;t discuss Cyrus the Great&amp;#39;s central role in allowing the Jews to return to Israel and certainly not his orders to rebuilt the Temple because this would prove Israel&amp;#39;s historical connection to the land and help justify its continued existence. It is this reason why Zarif also didn&amp;#39;t mention the short-lived, &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sasanian_conquest_and_occupation_of_Jerusalem&quot;&gt;Sasanian-aided Jewish conquest of Jerusalem in 614&lt;/a&gt; that was successful until Iran abandoned its Jewish allies to Byzantium, leading to massacres throughout the land.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Which is it?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Iran can&amp;#39;t have its Jews and kill them too: either it recognizes that Cyrus allowed the Jews to return to Israel and rebuild the Temple, thereby recognizing the right of the Jews to the land, or it does not. It cannot celebrate the King for liberating the Jews and ignore what this entailed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would just be nice if one of the many journalists interviewing him actually called him on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/09/Just-One-Question-for-FM-Zarif/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/09/Just-One-Question-for-FM-Zarif/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Why Obama&#39;s &#39;Muslim Grievances&#39; policy towards terrorism is so attractive and why it is fatally flawed.</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;The centerpiece of President Obama&amp;#39;s speeches at last month&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;Summit on Countering Violent Extremism&amp;quot; is the idea that the unnamed Islamic extremism is a result, not of radical ideology, but a reaction to &amp;quot;legitimate grievances&amp;quot; against America and the West.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listening to his words, it at first seems that the President understands that terrorism is not causally related to poverty and other economic &amp;quot;grievances,&amp;quot;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;poverty alone does not cause a person to become a terrorist, any more than poverty alone causes someone to become a criminal.  There are millions, billions of people who are poor and are law-abiding and peaceful and tolerant, and are trying to advance their lives and the opportunities for their families.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is incredibly important because it is established fact that wealthy, highly-educated people have become terrorists and billions of poor people have not:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;IMG SRC=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/aAcsVnH.jpg&quot; ALT=&quot;terror&quot; WIDTH=300 HEIGHT=350&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But right after the President acknowledges this, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.whitehouse.gov/the-press-office/2015/02/19/remarks-president-summit-countering-violent-extremism-february-19-2015&quot;&gt;he backtracks&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But when people -- especially young people -- feel entirely trapped in impoverished communities, where there is no order and no path for advancement, where there are no educational opportunities, where there are no ways to support families, and no escape from injustice and the humiliations of corruption -- that feeds instability and disorder, and makes those communities ripe for extremist recruitment.  And we have seen that across the Middle East and we&amp;#39;ve seen it across North Africa.  So if we’re serious about countering violent extremism, we have to get serious about confronting these economic grievances.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea that Islamic Extremism (I&amp;#39;ll use the term even though Obama won&amp;#39;t) can be properly countered by addressing alleged economic grievances is bunk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the President did say something here that actually is true:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;that feeds instability and disorder, and makes those communities ripe for extremist recruitment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course someone who has nothing to lose and feels oppressed is more likely to buy into a radical ideology that tells him he isn&amp;#39;t at fault and that all his problems are caused by America or the Jews. We know this is true because it was exactly the environment in which the Nazis rose to power in Germany. A humiliated people, ravaged by war, economy in tatters, were offered a vision in which they could claim to be the victims. It wasn&amp;#39;t German warmongering that caused their dire predicament, it was the schemes of the Jews. In order to be the world superpower Germany was and should be, all you had to do was buy into an imagined past based on centuries of well-crafted anti-Semitism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it wasn&amp;#39;t economic distress alone that caused the rise of Nazism (many countries are ravaged by war and don&amp;#39;t end up turning to genocidal anti-Semitism). There were still plenty of wealthy, upper-class Germans who bought into Nazism - not because of the economic situation - but because it spoke to them as German Nationalists and fed on their history of anti-Semitism. It was these two factors that also provided the foundation for those more economically depressed Germans to see the Nazis as the answer to their problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This historical precedent also offers us a window into how we can achieve victory over radical Islam. When the Allies went to war against Nazi Germany, they didn&amp;#39;t seek to end the war and make peace, they sought nothing less than complete victory and submission from the vanquished. After this was achieved, a process of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Denazification&quot;&gt;Denazification&lt;/a&gt; was enacted to undo the decades of brainwashing from Goebbels&amp;#39;s propaganda machine. This was largely successful, but it overlooked a problem we are dealing with today: Denazification was only enacted in Germany and Austria, ignoring the Islamic world that was so receptive to the Nazi&amp;#39;s supremacist and anti-Semitic ideology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Lc8Ea5J.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bundesarchiv Bild 146-1987-004-09A, Amin al Husseini und Adolf Hitler&quot; title=&quot;Bundesarchiv Bild 146-1987-004-09A, Amin al Husseini und Adolf Hitler&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This message was widely accepted in the Muslim world with groups like the Muslim Brotherhood, whose founder, Hassan al-Banna, allying themselves with the Nazis and taking this message as their own. Despite their active collaboration with the Nazis, the Muslim Brotherhood was not prosecuted after the war and many Nazi war criminals a found safe haven among them. Booksellers on the streets of Cairo still openly sell copies of Mein Kampf - though without the sections describing Arabs as one of the lowest races of humanity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ycPSmTI.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Hezbollah Salute&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The links between &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Relations_between_Nazi_Germany_and_the_Arab_world&quot;&gt;Nazism and the roots of Islamic Terrorism&lt;/a&gt; are well documented but completely ignored by Leftists like Barack Obama. Once a radical ideology takes up residence in a community, it cannot be excised without being countered on its own terms. Nazism wasn&amp;#39;t defeated in Germany just by building up its economy and getting out of work Germans jobs, that would have just made Nazi Germany stronger. Nazism was only defeated when it was vanquished militarily and the population reeducated. This is exactly what needs to happen in the war against Radical Islam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;If this is so clearly the case, then why exactly is the view that President Obama is presenting - economic grievances against the West are the driving factor in breeding terrorism - so compelling for many, especially on the Left? &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is the same reason why anti-Israel, &lt;a href=&quot;http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/02/blue-and-whitewashing/&quot;&gt;Blue-and-Whitewashing&lt;/a&gt; groups like J Street are gaining in popularity as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In promoting their &amp;quot;pro-peace&amp;quot; agenda, J Street lobbies for American pressure against Israel (and only against Israel) to make concessions and compromises for peace. This is because, in their view, the only reason there is no peace is because Israel refuses to end the occupation. Facts have no place in this discussion, so pointing out that &lt;strong&gt;Arab rejectionism and terrorism pre-dated the occupation&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;that the Palestinians have rejected four peace plans in the past 15 years and torpedoed numerous attempts at negotiation&lt;/strong&gt;, does nothing to change the view of these groups. To them, everything is Israel&amp;#39;s fault.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;But why would such an idea be so attractive to the Jews who join J Street?&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is surprisingly simple: if everything is Israel&amp;#39;s fault, if peace is absent only because of what Israel does, then Israel alone can change this. Jews can do very little to change the rejectionist, anti-Semitic, and pro-terror views of the Palestinians, but if all of those are really just a reaction to things Jews do (and not what Jews are) then there is an easy answer to the problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is exactly why President Obama desperately needs to believe that Islamic Terrorism is a result of American policy and not a rejection of American values by embracing an opposing ideology. If everything is really a result of &amp;quot;legitimate grievances&amp;quot; caused by the United States, then President Obama just needs to address those issues and the problem will go away. But, if Islamic terrorists and their supporters actually believe what they believe for reasons independent of the US, then only a massive program of Dejihadification can stop them, and that is a much more complicated and messy matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only is this difficult because it involves militarily defeating ISIS and replacing its ideology, but it is more complicated than Denazification because Nazism was only a political ideology and political ideologies can be changed and countered by rival ideologies and by outsiders. However, the Salafi Jihadism that is practiced by extremists in ISIS, Hamas, and Boko Haram, is believed by them to be the only authentic form of their religion. Non-Muslims cannot counter this ideology with an alternate form of Islam, only Muslims can do that. So even if ISIS is defeated militarily, unless the Muslim world creates an antidote for radical Jihadism in the form of a more moderate and modern Islam, another will just pop up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that is precisely why President Obama&amp;#39;s narrative is doomed to fail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The shocking words of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jstreetwatch.org/#!J-Street-CoFounder-Israel-Aint-a-Very-Good-Idea/c1nni/010525D6-93A6-402C-8526-3AAB2662EBB5&quot;&gt;J Street&amp;#39;s co-founder, Daniel Levy&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/gZFBgLb.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Daniel Levy&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bottom line: if we&amp;#39;re all wrong, and the collective Jewish presence in the Middle East can only survive by the sword, it cannot be accepted, it&amp;#39;s not about what we do - sound familiar? They hate us for what we are, not what we do - if that&amp;#39;s true, then Israel really ain&amp;#39;t a very good idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This disturbing idea, proudly stated by J Street&amp;#39;s leader, is exactly what President Obama was saying at the &amp;quot;Summit on Countering Violent Extremism.&amp;quot; You just have to switch out a few words:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bottom Line: if we&amp;#39;re all wrong, and the Islamist ideology exists because its followers actually believe in its message and see it as authentic Islam, it&amp;#39;s not about what we do - sound familiar? They hate us for what we are, not what we do - if that&amp;#39;s true, then America really ain&amp;#39;t a very good idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The self-centered nature of Liberals will be our undoing if not actively countered. This idea that everything is really the fault of Israel and the West can be comforting because it imbues Westerners with an inflated sense of self-importance making them think they have the power to enact change on their own, can only lead to our own destruction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is exactly why it is also so dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/08/Muslim-Grievances/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/08/Muslim-Grievances/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Will Israel Settle the Entire West Bank?</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;h4&gt;Sure, just give it 5,000 years. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#39;ve heard it a million times: Israeli settlements are making a Two-State Solution impossible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Two-State Solution is the unquestionable, divinely ordained goal of the Left, and since we are told that settlements are making this not viable or have already made it impossible, this is a huge problem, worthy of global attention and condemnation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is accepted as fact by the average news consumer. But let&amp;#39;s take a few minutes and see if it actually holds up to the facts (hint, it doesn&amp;#39;t).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order for the settlements to pose a threat to the Two-State Solution, they would need to take up a substantial amount of land. From a cursory view of the media and its obsessive, witch-hunt-like focus on the issue, one would certainly believe they do. So that begs the question:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;How much land do the settlements take up anyway?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of going to the Israeli government or the settler groups themselves, which one might expect to downplay the size of the settlements, let&amp;#39;s ask B&amp;#39;Tselem, the leftist Israeli &amp;quot;human rights organization&amp;quot; that spends most of its time and resources demonizing Israel when its &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.algemeiner.com/2014/10/05/israeli-human-rights-group-btselem-admits-holocaust-denier-in-ranks-video/&quot;&gt;employees aren&amp;#39;t denying the Holocaust&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thirdworldtraveler.com/Israel/Israeli_Settlements.html&quot;&gt;According to Yehezkel Lein&lt;/a&gt;, a researcher at B&amp;#39;Tselem, the built-up areas of the settlements take up... &lt;strong&gt;1.7%!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;IMG SRC=&quot;http://www.mappery.com/maps/Jewish-Settlements-in-West-Bank-Map.jpg&quot; ALT=&quot;some text&quot; WIDTH=300 HEIGHT=500&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now you&amp;#39;re probably thinking, that can&amp;#39;t be right! They must take up more land than that or else they wouldn&amp;#39;t make headlines like they do. Well, let&amp;#39;s now go to the Palestinians and see what they have to say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.haaretz.com/news/diplomacy-defense/erekat-olmert-offered-palestinians-territorial-equivalent-of-west-bank-1.393484&quot;&gt;According to Saeb Erekat&lt;/a&gt;, the chief Palestinian &amp;quot;peace&amp;quot; negotiator and Abbas confidant, said in 2011 that the built-up areas of the settlements take up... &lt;strong&gt;1.1% of the West Bank!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This news is probably very jarring to you. Could it be that the settlements take up just over a single percent of the West Bank? Surely the municipal boundaries take up more land and that is the cause of the global outrage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, let&amp;#39;s ask Yehezkel Lein of B&amp;#39;Tselem again. How much land do the settlements take up if you include their municipal boundaries? An astonishing, astronomical, asymmetrical, astounding... &lt;strong&gt;5.1%!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;But what about the additional land administered to by the local regional councils and military zones? Those end up taking roughly 40% of the West Bank. You&amp;#39;re trying to fool me with numbers!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#39;re right, there is more land that is outside of the municipal boundaries that is controlled by Israel. This includes Area C and parts of Area B. But this was part of an arrangement the Palestinians themselves agreed to during Oslo. More to the point, since this is area is almost entirely uninhabited and only contains military outposts or bases, it can easily be evacuated and transferred to the Palestinians if by some miracle they ever agreed to peace and we were able to trust them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, Israel has a history of withdrawing from territory and removing settlements and military bases in exchange for peace and in attempts to create conditions conducive for peace, but instead each time the territory has become a haven for terrorists:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/pnfRR3h.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Land Concessions for Peace&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1979 - Camp David Accords Israel agreed to a full withdrawal from the Sinai in exchange for peace. Stability reigned for years, but now ISIS affiliates have taken over wide swaths of territory and have attacked both Egypt and Israel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2000 - Israel unilaterally withdrew from all of Southern Lebanon, which was subsequently taken over by Hezbollah who filled it with rockets aimed at Israeli cities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2005 - Israel unilaterally withdrew from Gaza and 4 settlements in Samaria only to have Gaza overrun by Hamas 2 years later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;2006 - Israeli voters elect Kadima, a party who&amp;#39;s sole platform was withdrawing from most of the West Bank, just as was done in Gaza a year prior. This was scrapped after the Palestinians voted in Hamas and it violently seized power in Gaza.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Israel also agreed to withdrawal at Camp David in 2000, The Clinton Parameters and Taba in 2001, and Olmert&amp;#39;s Proposal in 2008. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is historical fact that Israel has committed itself to withdrawal and the removal of settlements when it believes doing so will help the cause of peace. It just happens that each time, abandoned territory has been used to make war instead. It isn&amp;#39;t the settlements that are preventing peace or even a division of the land, but rather Palestinian rejectionism and violence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But even in the face of all this, Israeli building in Judea and Samaria has been limited to &lt;strong&gt;just over 1% of the territory.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So let&amp;#39;s be clear about this: &lt;strong&gt;after nearly 50 years of Israeli control of Judea and Samaria, Israel has built up a little more than 1% of the land, which is expanded to only 5% with the municipal boundaries.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world is right. At this rate, Israel will settle the entire West Bank... &lt;strong&gt;in about 5000 years.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Alert the presses!&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/06/Will-Israel-Settle-the-Entire-West-Bank/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/06/Will-Israel-Settle-the-Entire-West-Bank/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Deconstructing Jon Stewart&#39;s attack on #NetanyahuSpeech</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;If any of you tuned in to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://thedailyshow.cc.com/full-episodes/hmp9gu/march-3--2015---sigourney-weaver&quot;&gt;Daily Show&lt;/a&gt; last night, I&amp;#39;m sure you weren&amp;#39;t surprised by the singular focus on Netanyahu and the incredibly childish way in which Jon Stewart deals with his speech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We at the Judean People&amp;#39;s Front - ever the optimists - were still shocked by the deranged views given by Acheinu Jon. We don&amp;#39;t countenance Splitters, so we&amp;#39;ve decided to take the episode apart point by point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The way Stewart opens the show leaves no room for any doubt about what he is going to be discussing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shalom, my friends welcome to a very special night. Benyamin (sic) Netanyahu addressed Congress today in observance of the Jewish holiday of Suuk-on-it Mr. President. It was a Festival of Slights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/qfiYjX0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Suuk-on-it Mr. President&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Why didn&amp;#39;t Boehner consult with the White House?&amp;quot; Stewart asks incredulously, before spending over half a minute merely mocking the speaker instead of discussing whether or not there was actually a snub. Is Congress a co-equal branch of government with the Executive that has every right to invite a foreign leader to address it? It is, but not according to Jon Stewart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He clearly knows better than the both the US and Israeli governments, even if he can&amp;#39;t even pronounce Bibi&amp;#39;s first name properly. We&amp;#39;re sure he is making his childhood Hebrew teacher proud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stewart continues:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Benjamin Netanyahu was on hand to explain to OUR Congress why OUR President should not be negotiating a nuclear deal with Iran.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each time, Stewart accentuates the word &amp;quot;our&amp;quot; to show that this is &lt;strong&gt;our&lt;/strong&gt; government and Israel has no right sticking its nose in &lt;strong&gt;our&lt;/strong&gt; business. Of course the fact that it was OUR government that invited him in the first place is irrelevant because it was the Legislature doing the inviting instead of the Executive. But for liberals like Stewart, there aren&amp;#39;t three branches of the US government, only President Obama.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/3XbEiu3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bibi&amp;#39;s Big Adventure&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then of course is the obligatory allusion to electioneering, because clearly the only reason Bibi would be speaking to Congress would be to boost his poll numbers and not because he genuinely believes in his message. Of course Stewart doesn&amp;#39;t mention that Netanyahu invited opposition leader Issac Herzog to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesofisrael.com/herzog-says-he-wont-address-congress-with-netanyahu/&quot;&gt;join him in addressing Congress&lt;/a&gt; and was refused. He doesn&amp;#39;t mention that Kirk-Menendez is coming up for a vote soon and Netanyahu wouldn&amp;#39;t be able to go address Congress while trying to cobble together a new coalition, a process that can take weeks if not months. Stewart doesn&amp;#39;t mention any of this because his grasp of the situation is limited to only what Obama tells him he should be agreeing with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stewart then sets up the tape of Bibi explaining why he is going to Congress:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel I am representing all the citizens of Israel, even those who do not agree with me. A representative of the entire Jewish people. I feel a deep and sincere concern for the safety of all the citizens of Israel and the fate of our state and the fate of our people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/ZLC0jwV.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;I Speak for all Jews!&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stewart then gesticulates and shouts: &amp;quot;I speak for all Jews!... including the ones who don&amp;#39;t want me to... because those Jews are wrong,&amp;quot; before talking about the long Jewish tradition of arguing amongst ourselves as proof that Bibi does not in fact speak for all Jews.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A far more effective way to show that Bibi doesn&amp;#39;t speak for all Jews would be to play a video for the audience where Netanyahu says he is only &amp;quot;a&amp;quot; representative of the Jewish people, but not &amp;quot;the&amp;quot; representative of the Jewish people... What&amp;#39;s that? He did? I already quoted it but Stewart ignored the substance in favor of getting a laugh while misleading his audience? I can&amp;#39;t believe it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But of course Jon Stewart isn&amp;#39;t the first leftist Jew to manipulate Bibi&amp;#39;s words to make it seem as though he is arrogantly acting as the voice of all Jews. Just two days ago &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesofisrael.com/sen-feinstein-pans-netanyahu-over-claim-to-speak-for-all-jews/&quot;&gt;Senator Dianne Feinstein made the same accusation&lt;/a&gt;, referencing Bibi&amp;#39;s insistence of going to Paris after Jews were murdered in a kosher supermarket. But then also, he was careful to say he was &amp;quot;a&amp;quot; representative, not &amp;quot;the&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;the only&amp;quot; representative of the Jewish people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feinstein and Stewart know they can&amp;#39;t say Bibi doesn&amp;#39;t represent some Jews, so instead they lie and claim he said he represents them all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/K3uB6VO.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Batman Kippah&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stewart them makes some jokes about CNN hosting a debate between the anti-Israel leader of J Street, Jeremy Ben-Ami, and serial self-promoter, but outspoken defender of Israel Shmuley Boteach, asking, &amp;quot;When did CNN start hosting my family&amp;#39;s seders?&amp;quot; And mocks CNN for using a Jewish Star as their &lt;a href=&quot;http://content.videoblocks.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/NZYZNeu.gif&quot;&gt;new star-wipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He asks if they couldn&amp;#39;t get a Batman-style spinning yarmulke and jokes about CNN being shown in airports in this way:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/xr1JfAj.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;CNN Airports&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that he has the audience even more on his side with low-hanging jokes, Stewart continues:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How will the Obama administration handle this unprecedented eye-poke?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He then cuts to video of Obama talking up his pro-Israel credentials. One would think it would also be helpful here to mention that instead of poking Obama&amp;#39;s eye, Netanyahu was even more effusive in his praise of the President during his speech to Congress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But that isn&amp;#39;t the only thing Stewart intentionally leaves out. There is no discussion of the fact that Obama had &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/post-politics/wp/2015/02/25/susan-rice-netanyahus-speech-destructive/&quot;&gt;National Security Adviser Susan Rice&lt;/a&gt; say Netanyahu&amp;#39;s speech was &amp;quot;destructive of the fabric of the [US-Israel] relationship.&amp;quot; Such threatening language was clearly chosen to warn Israel that the relationship is not as &amp;quot;unbreakable&amp;quot; as President Obama often claims. Of course even the most casual news reader knows that in the run-up to the speech, there was unprecedented anger from Obama towards Israel, but this uncontested fact doesn&amp;#39;t fit Stewart&amp;#39;s message so he just leaves it out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stewart is known to use his Jewish background for jokes and even feigning anti-Semitism at times to get laughs. But his next statement, I think, went further than he has ever gone:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s how powerful Israel is. Their prime minister comes here, publicly slaps Obama in the face and the President&amp;#39;s response is &amp;quot;wha-nah, it&amp;#39;s ok, in fact you should know I&amp;#39;m buying him gloves so when he hits me it doesn&amp;#39;t hurt his hand as much.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Talking about a secret power that Israel has over the US government, at a time when there is a visual to back up the old anti-Semitic conspiracy theory is irresponsible to say the least. Are you telling me Stewart couldn&amp;#39;t come up with a joke without resorting to something like this? He should know better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stewart then attempts to &amp;quot;strike a balance&amp;quot; by joking about Joe Biden. Of course, they&amp;#39;re all softball jokes devoid of substance, but it lets him claim to treat both sides equally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next its time to cue the video of Obama asking what would have happened if Democrats had invited the French President to address Congress in the run up to the Iraq War. This is of course followed by the obligatory jokes about Freedom Fries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What Obama and Stewart fail to mention is that despite the personal dislike (some have called it enmity) the two leaders had for one another, President Bush never let it get personal or stand in the way of diplomacy. As &lt;a href=&quot;http://tws.io/1CzwzdB&quot;&gt;Elliott Abrams recently recounted&lt;/a&gt; Bush recognized the Franco-US relationship was more important than either of them and set up monthly meetings where both countries&amp;#39; National Security Advisors met in Washington. This allowed Bush and Chirac to maintain professional and diplomatic relations with one another while maintaining the distance needed to make it workable and crisis-free. Abrams noted, &amp;quot;It was a serious time commitment for the American and French officials, but that is because we were determined to quarantine bad personal chemistry and prevent it from infecting the entire relationship—a goal set by President Bush himself.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is clear from this insider&amp;#39;s take that had the Democrats taken the step to invite President Chirac to address Congress under Bush, there would have been no flare up or personal mud-slinging, because President Bush refused to act in such a petty manner, even with leaders he couldn&amp;#39;t stand. It is also worth remembering that back in 2013 when Obama refused Netanyahu&amp;#39;s request to address the Knesset (unlike President Bush and Clinton), Bibi didn&amp;#39;t say a word, still met with Obama, and didn&amp;#39;t create a crisis over it. He acted like a statesman and swallowed the snub for the greater good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this is all above Stewart&amp;#39;s shallow understanding of international politics so instead he makes outlandish claims that Republicans would have demanded Democrats inviting Chirac &amp;quot;be arrested for sedition and treason.&amp;quot; The idea that someone with such a large and impressionable audience can make such blatantly ridiculous accusations and only be called on it by the Judean People&amp;#39;s Front is shocking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point we were ready to turn off the episode but we powered through because we were still waiting for Stewart to, you know, actually discuss the speech itself (we&amp;#39;re almost 7 minutes into a 20 minute show where only the first 10 minutes are about the speech and still nothing). So finally Stewart says, &amp;quot;After all that build up I was pretty excited for the speech itself.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But before he can actually talk about the speech, he has to make the obligatory jokes about the standing ovations and applause Bibi received. &lt;em&gt;How dare people act like they actually want to hear what he has to say or show their support for America&amp;#39;s greatest ally in the Middle East?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stewart, in his Old Jewish man voice says, &amp;quot;It was a miracle, a standing ovation that was supposed to last for just one minute, miraculously lasted eight.&amp;quot; Sure it&amp;#39;s kind of funny, but for someone insisting on using their Jewishness for both humor and a guard against accusations of anti-Semitism, it might be nice if he knew that tonight is Purim not Chanukah...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally we get to hear some of the speech itself, but of course only a few, select lines that Stewart can subsequently manipulate:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It doesn&amp;#39;t block Iran&amp;#39;s path to the bomb; it paves Iran&amp;#39;s path to the bomb... Iran&amp;#39;s break-out time would be very short -- about a year by U.S. assessment, even shorter by Israel&amp;#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And it&amp;#39;s time for a circumcision joke because Israel cut a little off at the tip of the assessment. Classy as always Jon. He then follows up with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Holy sh*t, one year. Bibi, if Iran is that close, why didn&amp;#39;t you bring your urgent warning about Iran going nuclear sooner? Oh wait you did? (with a look of utter delight on his face) Apparently time was also running out 19 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cut to Bibi&amp;#39;s address to Congress in 1996:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this regime... were to acquire nuclear weapons this would presage catastrophic consequences. Only the United States can lead this vital international effort to stop the nuclearization of terrorist states. Time is running out, we have to act.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stewart proceeds to joke about Bibi not aging because he doesn&amp;#39;t understand the difference between the two warnings and what a breakout period really is. Back in 1996, Netanyahu was warning about a possibility. Iran&amp;#39;s nuclear program was still in its infancy, with only minor facilities and lacking in major technical know-how. Had we heeded his warnings and worked towards a nuclear-free deal with Iran then, before its leaders had openly declared they would accept nothing short of being a nuclear power, we probably wouldn&amp;#39;t be in this mess today. Moreover, the one year break-out period Bibi talks about is the same one Obama says is acceptable. The current deal under discussion assumes that because of the oversight involved, if Iran violates the agreement, they&amp;#39;ll need a year before they can create a nuclear bomb. This isn&amp;#39;t crying wolf, that is the assessment of the US intelligence services. But Stewart either doesn&amp;#39;t understand the difference between the two scenarios or he is willfully creating a false equivalence to mislead his viewers. Either way, he has no credibility on this issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is Stewart done manipulating old tapes of Netanyahu for his own purposes? Of course not, so now we get the second of only two video clips from the speech that ostensibly is the centerpiece of this episode:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the Middle East, Iran now dominates four Arab capitals Baghdad, Damascus, Beirut, and Sana&amp;#39;a.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To which Stewart remarks:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have to act, just look how Iran has expanded its power since the fall of Saddam Hussein and the destabilization in the region. I mean, what kind of idiot wouldn&amp;#39;t have seen that coming in 2002... oh shalom:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Md1l5Q9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bibi doesn&amp;#39;t age&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bibi on Sept 12, 2002: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you take out Saddam, Saddam&amp;#39;s regime, I guarantee you, that it will have enormous positive reverberations on the region. The reverberations of what happens with the collapse of Saddam&amp;#39;s regime could very well create an implosion in a neighboring regime like Iran.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Or the opposite&amp;quot; Stewart retorts as he happily jumps at his own setup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So caught up in playing &amp;quot;gotcha&amp;quot; Stewart fails to recognize that it wasn&amp;#39;t removing Saddam that led to the instability in Iraq today, but rather the premature abandonment pushed through by President Obama, who insisted on pulling out all American troops from Iraq after the Surge (which Obama opposed) had finally brought stability, which he eventually admitted &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://politicalticker.blogs.cnn.com/2008/09/25/fact-check-was-obama-against-the-troop-surge-in-iraq/&quot;&gt;succeeded beyond our wildest dreams.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; It would also behoove Stewart to remember that the 2009 attempted Green Revolution in Iran and Arab Spring followed the fall of Saddam just as Netanyahu said they would. However it never occurred to Bibi that America would have a President who would abandon those striving for freedom, throw our allies to the wolves, and squander every opportunity for positive change in the Middle East. Netanyahu was absolutely correct in his discussion of &amp;quot;positive reverberations&amp;quot; he just couldn&amp;#39;t foresee an Obama presidency that would ruin it all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stewart then bemoans that &amp;quot;in the House Chamber, there was no such reflecting [on Bibi&amp;#39;s past record of &amp;quot;false predictions&amp;quot;].&amp;quot; It never occurs to him that this may be because they know the history much better than he does. But who needs history when Stewart can make more jokes about applause before his final mic-drop:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether or not Netanyahu accomplished his goal of sabotaging a deal with Iran or mistakenly opened up a rift in US-Israeli relations, one thing is certain, the in-chamber response to this speech was by far the longest blow job a Jewish man has ever received.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You sure know how to make your mother schep Jon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course Netanyahu&amp;#39;s goal never was &amp;quot;sabatoging a deal with Iran&amp;quot; but preventing the signing of a bad deal with Iran that would allow it to continue to develop nuclear weapons. With the ten-year sunset clause, Iran doesn&amp;#39;t even have to violate the deal in order to get nukes, all it has to do is wait out the clock. Preventing this eventuality was Bibi&amp;#39;s goal, but Stewart didn&amp;#39;t have a whitty or low-brow rejoinder, so it fell to the cutting-room floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next 4 minute long segment is completely devoid of any substance, doesn&amp;#39;t talk about the speech at all, and is just a way for Stewart to make some jokes about the media and photoshop Bibi, Obama, and Khamenei in compromising positions. This was followed by an interview with Sigourney Weaver which was completely unrelated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So let&amp;#39;s do a quick recap: this 20 minute long episode - -allegedly all about Netanyahu&amp;#39;s speech - only spent half the time on a segment about the speech itself, and of those 10 minutes, only two lines were actually discussed. The rest of the time was spent on dick jokes and manipulating old clips to fit Stewart&amp;#39;s predetermined conclusions and mislead the audience on every point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This entire episode was useless as any sort of political commentary, which sadly is how it is seen by the majority of The Daily Show viewers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet again Israel was falsely flayed in the town square by Jon Stewart who uses his own Jewishness as a shield against critcisim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What a shanda.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/05/deconstructing-jon-stewarts-attack/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/03/05/deconstructing-jon-stewarts-attack/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>