<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title></title>
		<description>I asked for a media empire, but the Elders of Zion only gave me a Twitter account and a blog.</description>
		<link>http://judeanpf.com</link>
		<atom:link href="http://judeanpf.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Debunking the #FloodLibel</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;The heavy rains in Israel were exacerbated this week by a decision by the Hamas government in Gaza to open the dams on the borders of the Gaza Strip. By opening these dams, Israeli towns and roads were submerged in water disrupting traffic and putting many Israeli lives at risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A shop owner in Sderot &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesofisrael.com/rain-wind-prompt-road-closures-as-winter-weather-returns/&quot;&gt;complained&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“I don’t understand why this happened to us. The last time, the municipality told us that [there was flooding] because there was more rain than normal, and therefore the drainage system couldn’t handle it. But what happened this time? There was a normal amount of rain, and here we are, again with flooding, even worse than the last time.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clearly this shop owner was unaware of the nefarious actions taken by Hamas and its intentions to flood Israel. While Hamas has denied these actions, citing the fact that there is similar flooding in Gaza and that no dams exist for it to open even if it wanted to, Israel stuck to its assertion of Hamas culpability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Israeli government also reported that the Palestinian Authority in the West Bank has opened barrages leading to flooding in central and southern Israel. These claims were also denied.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above is obviously nonsense. Israel is flooding today due to heavy rains and not because of any dams Hamas opened. Hearing the story reported this way sounds completely ridiculous and immediately outs anyone parroting it a propagandist not a journalist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, year after year, this same narrative is churned out by the Palestinian media and picked up by news affiliates all over the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These news sources, hungry for a story that easily paints Israel as evil and Palestinians as victims jump on this without bothering to do the most basic research that would tell them:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There are no dams around Gaza to be opened as admitted by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.aljazeera.com/news/2015/02/gazans-flee-floods-caused-israel-dams-opening-150222115950849.html&quot;&gt;Al Jazeera in an uncharacteristically forceful retraction&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Israel suffers from the same exact flooding at the same exact time (see above videos).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In anticipation of the natural flooding, Israel facilitates the transfer of &lt;a href=&quot;http://honestreporting.com/dam-busted-palestinian-lie-exposed/&quot;&gt;heavy water pumps from the Palestinian Authority to Gaza&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The #FloodLibel hasn’t yet started to make major rounds this year, but when it does (and it will), be ready to debunk it with this easy to use chart:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.israellycool.com/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/FloodLibel-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bibi v. Bujie&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2016/02/24/Debunking-the-FloodLibel/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2016/02/24/Debunking-the-FloodLibel/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>When The Left Got It Right</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, opposition leader Isaac Herzog of the Zionist Union party, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesofisrael.com/herzog-for-now-two-state-solution-unrealistic/&quot;&gt;announced a major change in policy for Israel’s Left&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“I don’t see a possibility at the moment of implementing the two-state solution. I want to yearn for it, I want to move toward it, I want negotiations, I sign on to it and I am obligated to it, but I don’t see the possibility of doing it right now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We would like to welcome Mr. Herzog to the reality that the rest of us have accepted for some time now. However, our realities are not quite the same just yet. That is because while Netanyahu and the Right have recognized this fact for years, unlike Herzog, when Bibi says this out loud, he is roundly condemned for being “anti-peace.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in March of 2015, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/2015/03/17/world/middleeast/benjamin-netanyahu-campaign-settlement.html&quot;&gt;before the most recent elections, the Prime Minister said&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“I think that anyone who is going to establish a Palestinian state today and evacuate lands is giving attack grounds to the radical Islam against the state of Israel.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While Herzog left the door open to more idealism and hope, waxing poetic about “yearning,” “moving” and “negotiating,” the message is exactly the same: under current conditions, it is impossible to create a Palestinian state and neither will allow it to happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, why is one condemned while the other supported? Because the world today is wedded to the idea that Left = good and Right = bad in the same way that Palestinians = good/victim and Israel = evil/oppressor. This narrative must be guarded at all costs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the first casualty is the facts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/bk5Zhlm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bibi v. Bujie&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;##Join the conversation on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.israellycool.com/2016/01/20/when-the-left-got-it-right/&quot;&gt;Israellycool&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2016/01/20/When-The-Left-Got-It-Right/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2016/01/20/When-The-Left-Got-It-Right/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Did Abbas Actually Condemn Dafna Meir&#39;s Murder?</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;The media has been making a lot of noise recently about Mahmoud Abbas’s “condemnation” of the brutal murder of Dafna Meir in front of her daughter. Speaking on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.i24news.tv/en/news/israel/diplomacy-defense/99674-160119-escalation-feared-after-israeli-settlements-stabbings&quot;&gt;Palestinian TV broadcast from the Church of the Nativity&lt;/a&gt;, the Palestinian dictator said, “We are concerned over every drop of blood from any person.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How wonderfully heartfelt and specific. You can really feel his concern for Dafna’s husband, four children and two foster children who are now mourning their mother and wife who was stabbed to death in her own home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is very difficult to coax any Palestinian leader to condemn violence against Jews. But in this case, Abbas has not actually condemned anything. But this is worse than the standard “we condemn all violence” line from the Palestinian leadership. That is because if we look at Abbas’s previous statements, this is actually a dressed up version of his previous calls to violence!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back on 16 September 2015, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wsj.com/articles/abbas-we-welcome-every-drop-of-blood-spilled-in-jerusalem-1445209820&quot;&gt;he said the following on Palestinian TV&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“We welcome every drop of blood spilled in Jerusalem. This is pure blood, clean blood, blood on its way to Allah. With the help of Allah, every martyr will be in heaven, and every wounded will get his reward.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, Abbas &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; concerned about “every drop of blood,” but he is concerned that not enough is being spilled!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He even makes this clear in the rest of his speech that is ignored or downplayed by the media. Abbas continues, saying, “the resistance will continue through peaceful means, and we will not call for anything else… We will stand firm on our land, and we will stay the course.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Abbas is not condemning the attack in Otniel, he is reiterating his call for bloodshed, while at the same time claiming that Palestinian stabbing attacks on Jews are peaceful!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is of course nothing new for the Palestinian leadership, but at least the PA is usually the one who says one thing in English and the exact opposite in Arabic. In this case, the media is doing Abbas’s job for him and ascribing false meaning to his words in their vain attempt to paint this extremist terrorist as a moderate peace partner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Share this poster to let the world know you’re not fooled by Abbas’s and the media’s deception:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/o3E7Gcy.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Two-Faced&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;##Join the conversation on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.israellycool.com/2016/01/19/did-abbas-actually-condemn-dafna-meirs-murder/&quot;&gt;Israellycool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2016/01/19/Abbas-Condemnation/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2016/01/19/Abbas-Condemnation/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>World Hypocrisy On Display In Wake of Stabbing in Paris</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Today, the one year anniversary of the Charlie Hebdo and Hyper Cache attacks, a Jihadist armed with a butcher’s knife and fake suicide vest (according to initial reports), was shot dead while shouting “Allahu Akabar” and attempting to kill French police officers in Paris. After he was neutralized, the police found two pieces of paper on him, one with an image of the ISIS flag and another with a handwritten note in Arabic claiming responsibility for the attack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/1zrONla.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Stabber&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a scene all too familiar to Israelis, however the international reaction to it, sadly, is not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There have been no calls on the French government to exercise “restraint” in its reactions to this terror attack. Nor have there been calls for France to negotiate with ISIS or establish a radical Islamist state on French soil. There also have been no foreign government officials condemning the Paris police for excessive force or carrying out an extrajudicial killing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same is true of the reactions to the Islamist hatchet attack in Queens, NY in 2014, the car ramming attack in Saint-Jean-sur-Richelieu, Quebec in the same year or of the car ramming and stabbing death of British Fusilier Lee Rigby in 2013 or any of the other numerous “low-level” terror attacks around the world recently.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what is different between these attacks and those carried out daily in Israel today?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The attackers in all cases have been radical Islamists. They all used low-tech weapons to carry out or attempt to carry out murders. Some have openly pledged allegiance to terrorist groups and others appear only to have been inspired by them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are only three real differences:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The location: Israel&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The target: Jews&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The frequency: Daily&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are numerous excuses for the double standards:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But Israel is bombing the Palestinians!” Is France not bombing ISIS?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But they’re attacking soldiers!” Lee Rigby was a soldier and the victims in France today were police officers (not to mention that the vast majority of Israeli victims are civilians, not soldiers).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But Palestinians don’t have a state of their own!” So we should give ISIS the Caliphate it wants? Would that stop the terror?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are excuses that lack any moral clarity or understanding of the threat of radical Jihad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fact of the matter is that if you see two attacks, both carried out by radical Islamists, both attempts to stab someone to death but only consider it terrorism when the intended victim is not Jewish, well there’s a word for that kind of hypocrisy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that word is anti-Semitism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Join the conversation on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.israellycool.com/2016/01/08/world-hypocrisy-on-display-in-wake-of-stabbing-in-paris/&quot;&gt;Israellycool&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2016/01/08/World-Hypocrisy/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2016/01/08/World-Hypocrisy/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>AJ+ Exposé Exposes More Than Intended</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;AJ+, Al Jazeera’s hip younger sister digital network, recently released a short video exploring the Balata “refugee” camp in Samaria. It was clearly set up to make the viewer incredibly sympathetic to the residents there but it actually showed just how ridiculous the Palestinian refugees’ claims to that status is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-video&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p lang=&quot;en&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;God willing, we will return.&amp;quot;&amp;#10;&amp;#10;Meet Ahmad, an 18-year-old Palestinian living in the largest West Bank refugee camp:&amp;#10;&lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/hPQcbaiQbB&quot;&gt;https://t.co/hPQcbaiQbB&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; AJ+ (@ajplus) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ajplus/status/679695257596903424&quot;&gt;December 23, 2015&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dena Takruri, who has made a career out of demonizing Israel and mythologizing Palestinian victimhood, reprises her role in her interview with Balata “refugee” Ahmad Khader. He appears to be in his early twenties and is well dressed in a button down over a sweater and jeans (which is also my go to outfit) and he is by no means starving.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/IiXJND8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Khader and Takruri&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps unwittingly, Ms. Takruri begins by highlighting the most contradictory aspect of all Palestinian “refugee” camps: their permanence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“The crazy thing is &lt;strong&gt;you would think that a refugee camp would be a temporary type of thing,&lt;/strong&gt; but as you’re seeing, these generations are growing up here born and raised. So his family was exiled, they became refugees from Jaffa in 1948. They came here in 1950 and they’ve been here ever since. &lt;strong&gt;So it’s become a permanent thing.&lt;/strong&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/6I7w9zs.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Armani Refugee&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Another permanent refugee wearing Armani)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This camp, which is essentially a permanent town in the heart of Palestinian controlled territory, has been running for roughly 65 years. Mr. Khader and his father (it seems) were both born there and yet they are still called refugees. His grandfather moved 53 kilometers from Jaffa to this area just outside of Nablus. This is roughly the same distance between Washington DC and Baltimore, not exactly a long journey. By any definition other than the one cynically used by UNRWA, Mr. Khader and his family are not refugees. They were not forced from their homes, they have citizenship in the Palestinian Authority and even his grandfather, who remained within the boundaries of Mandatory Palestine, would not be considered a refugee. But here is his grandson giving a tour of his pre-packaged misery for gullible Westerners to consume online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/C3pY2hg.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;UN&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ms. Takruri simply says the Khaders were “exiled from Jaffa,” but this is not the case at all. Mr. Khader later in the interview says, “They [his grandparents] told me that they were hoping to come back. They just turned off the stove and left.” Not that they were forced out of their home or that soldiers loaded them on a truck and drove them out of the city. They took some belongings and left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s more, Jaffa is probably the worst example an anti-Israel activist could cite as an example of “Israeli brutality.” There are several important aspects of the battle for Jaffa that must be taken into consideration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, Jaffa was slated to remain as part of the Arab State under the UN Partition Plan. This means that had the Arabs accepted peace from the beginning, Mr. Khader’s grandfather would never have left his home, there would never have been any refugees - from Jaffa or elsewhere - and this video never would have been made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Second, much of the disaster was precipitated by the Arab leadership and foreign militias. Whether by spreading rumors about false atrocities committed by the Zionists or by the foreign fighters, mainly Egyptian Muslim Brotherhood men, acting more like conquerors than saviors with Nimr al Khatib writing, “The inhabitants were more afraid of their defenders-saviours than of the Jews their enemies,” In fact, the leader of the Arab irregular forces, Abdul Wahab ‘Ali Shihaini, famously stated, &lt;strong&gt;“I do not mind [the] destruction [of] Jaffa if we secure [the] destruction [of] Tel Aviv.”&lt;/strong&gt; It’s hard to find a better example of the Arab objective in 1948 than that. (p.114, Benny Morris, The Birth of the Palestinian Refugee Problem Revisited)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hard but not impossible as Mahmoud Abbas picked up this baton of self-destructive anti-Semitism in 2013 when he said it was better for Palestinians to die in Syria than give up their “right of return” &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.maannews.com/Content.aspx?id=557940&quot;&gt;by accepting Israel’s offer to let them move to Judea and Samaria&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Third, many “Jaffans” were nothing of the kind. There were many fellahin who had recently moved to the city for work and simply returned to their original homes as Morris recounts, saying, “Country folk who earlier had migrated to the town &lt;strong&gt;were now moving back to their villages&lt;/strong&gt;. By the end of December [four months before Jaffa’s conquest], [Haganah Intelligence] reported that some ‘60 per cent’ of Jaffa’s Christians had left.” (p. 110) These made up part of the 15-25,000 “Jaffans” who abandoned the city by the end of 1947. (p. 111)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fourth,  this was not a one-sided conflict; over 7,000 Jews fled from Jaffa by mid-January 1948. (p. 110) Clearly this was not one side expelling the other but civilians on both sides leaving a war zone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that the history is settled, we can get back to the present where Mr. Khader, completely unprompted, drops this bombshell:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“We can live outside the refugee camp.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s that? He openly admits he doesn’t have to live there, that he actively chooses to live in the camp? That’s a bit of information you usually need to pry out with unrelenting patience and probing questions. So why is he so open about this?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“But if we give up the camp that means we give up our principles, the right of return. We always hope not to leave the camp and live somewhere else. We hope to go back to Jaffa, to our land, where my grandfather was born.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s right, because if he were to live somewhere else in the PA, that would mean admitting he will never actually move to Jaffa. This of course is obvious to anyone with eyes but making peace with reality has never been easy for the Palestinians. However, even this explanation does not really hold any water. There are millions of Palestinians around the world who are citizens of other countries, who don’t live in refugee camps and yet they also loudly insist on their “right of return,” so why couldn’t Mr. Khader move to, say, Rawabi, get a job, build himself a nice house, start a family and then should the conditions present themselves insist on moving to Jaffa?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mr. Khader could certainly do all this, but were he to leave the camp, he would also have to leave behind all the benefits he gets from UNRWA - housing, health care, education… - all provided free of charge. So he remains a “refugee” in the town he and his father were born in, in a territory of which he is a full citizen and yet Ms. Takruri dutifully accepts his romantic explanation without the slightest hint of journalistic inquisitiveness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What he says next is actually incredibly important, which is why the AJ+ interviewer completely ignores it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Because our sense of belonging at the end of the day is to our original cities. To Jaffa, and Haifa and Acre and our land from 1948.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in the 1940s, Palestinian nationalism was almost entirely confined to a few urban elites while the mass of the Arab population had many different, often competing identities. While pan-Arabism and pan-Islamism were gaining many followers, they were often added on top of a more localized identity focused around an individual’s specific town or city, clan, tribe and family. It appears that this localized identity has been passed down to generations who have never even lived in those towns. So, for all the pageantry and pomp and circumstance of Abbas’s flag ceremonies and statehood recognition, many of these “refugees” don’t seem to care about Palestine as a whole at all. While they fly the Palestinian colors and sing Palestinian songs, this nationalism is shallow and fragmented.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mr. Khader seems to realize his mistake in revealing this when he says,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“The Palestinian people are all one, sure, but why would I leave Balata camp and go live somewhere else when if I go settle somewhere else, I’ll be from there. I’ll give up my right of return. We don’t want to give that up… that’s our dream. &lt;strong&gt;That’s what we were raised on. There’s no alternative to the right of return.&lt;/strong&gt; I’m from Jaffa, which means I have to go back to Jaffa. &lt;strong&gt;If I don’t go back, maybe my son will. Maybe my grandchild. But someone from our lineage will return.&lt;/strong&gt; That’s the idea.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Mr. Khader, gaining a Palestinian state where he can build a life for himself and his family is of no importance. The only thing that matters to him, because he was “raised on” it, is “returning” to Jaffa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Takruri then asks about Mr. Khader’s grandfather and he says, “I’m sure you never expected that one day someone would take you out of our home put you in a refugee camp and say, “Now live.””&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course no one expects this to happen and that would certainly be a horrible thing. However, none of this happened to the elder Khader at all! Ahmad admits that his grandfather was not kicked out of his home but rather left on his own. He also freely admits that he is not forced to live in the refugee camp and can leave any time he wants but chooses to stay of his own volition. The only part of this bogus story that Khader doesn’t tell is that it wasn’t Israel that built Balata but rather Jordan! While all the Arabs who stayed in Israel were given citizenship and never put in any camps, Jordan forced these “refugees” into camps despite offering them citizenship!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/zgWVeAe.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Martyrs&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(The Khader family home covered in “martyr” posters)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This farce of a video ends with Khader saying, “We’re certain that we’ll return and God willing, we will return.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How sweet. How hopeful. How ridiculous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just as the militia leaders of 1948 were happy to see Jaffa burn if it meant also destroying Tel Aviv, and Abbas is happy to see thousands of Palestinians die in Syria if it means others will still remain to destroy the Jewish State, people like Ahmad Khader are perfectly happy to see their families suffer for generations as long as it means eventually being able to destroy Israel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poor kid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Join the conversation at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.israellycool.com/2015/12/25/aj-expose-exposes-more-than-intended/&quot;&gt;IsraellyCool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/12/25/AJ+-Expose-Exposes-More-Than-Intended/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/12/25/AJ+-Expose-Exposes-More-Than-Intended/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>#BDSFail: Jewish Student Unanimously Beats Ethics Probe After Standing Up To Anti-Israel Protesters</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;The Judean People’s Front is proud to report that the latest BDS attempt to silence pro-Israel voices on college campuses has failed miserably!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/h3rRyb7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jesse Arm&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On November 19 - the same day that Palestinian terror attacks killed 2 Israelis, 1 Palestinian and an &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.israellycool.com/2015/11/24/watch-moment-of-silence-for-ezra-schwartz-zl/&quot;&gt;American Jew&lt;/a&gt; - Students Allied for Freedom and Equality (SAFE), an anti-Israel group at the University of Michigan, erected a mock checkpoint on campus. While walking to class sophomore and Central Student Government representative, Jesse Arm, challeneged the protesters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/qqcFZCc.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Wall&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The protest included students dressed as Israeli soldiers and two large walls with a dove in a sniper’s cross-hairs, a poorly drawn version of &lt;a href=&quot;http://elderofziyon.blogspot.com/2012/07/debunking-map-that-lies.html&quot;&gt;the map that lies&lt;/a&gt; and “TO EXIST IS TO RESIST” written in large red letters. Mr. Arm confronted the protesters about their provocative message questioning both the taste and timing of the event.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After this brief encounter, the Central Student Government, at the urging of SAFE, called for an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.michigandaily.com/section/news/csg-meeting-2&quot;&gt;ethics probe to determine if Mr. Arm should be expelled from the student government&lt;/a&gt;. Unfortunately for SAFE, their own video recording of the event (which has yet to be released to the wider public) was to prove their own undoing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After watching the video, Mr. Arm was unanimously vindicated as it showed he did not engage in any form of intimidation, hate speech or aggression and despite the fact that it happened on the same day as a fellow American Jewish student was murdered by Palestinian jihadists, Mr. Arm conducted himself respectfully though forcefully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The response from the Ethics Committee was unanimous, unambiguous and precedent-setting given that this was the first time an ethics probe had ever been initiated at the University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Below are the highlights from the investigative report (all emphasis added):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommendation&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After reviewing video evidence and hearing testimonies from involved parties, the Central Student Government Ethics Committee has &lt;strong&gt;unanimously decided to recommend that the Assembly take no action against Representative Jesse Arm&lt;/strong&gt; for his involvement in the incident on the Diag. Representative Arm &lt;strong&gt;did not engage in unethical behavior or engage in conduct unbecoming of a representative&lt;/strong&gt;. Article VIII, Section 1 of the Constitution of the Student Body of the Ann Arbor Campus of the University of Michigan states that &lt;strong&gt;“no authority, academic or civil, shall infringe on a student’s freedom of speech, freedom to peacefully assemble, or freedom to demonstrate grievances.”&lt;/strong&gt; Just as the SAFE had the right to peacefully assemble in the Diag, &lt;strong&gt;Representative Jesse Arm had the right to voice his opinion.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Application&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Members of our community and Representatives of the Assembly may question whether a minor warning, formal warning, or formal reprimand may have been appropriate in this situation. The Constitution of the Student Body states that the Constitution has supremacy over any provision of another student code, including Central Student Government’s Operating Procedure. Article VIII, Section 3 of the Constitution states that “students shall be free from all rules and regulations not uniform in nature or not fully and clearly formulated.” Without clear definitions or standards, &lt;strong&gt;the Committee believes that we cannot issue a warning.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Ethics Committee took up this investigation and went through this process with no precedent. &lt;strong&gt;We were informed that this is the first Ethics Committee investigation ever.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Representatives should be held to a higher standard than the average student. However, while Representatives of the Assembly do represent all of their constituents, &lt;strong&gt;we do not shed our own personal opinions and beliefs when we decide to run for office&lt;/strong&gt;. Representative Arm has the right to engage in discourse. &lt;strong&gt;Representative Arm avoided physical violence, and members of SAFE testified that they did not believe Representative Arm incurred any emotional violence or any hateful speech on those present&lt;/strong&gt;. His language could be interpreted as hurtful just as SAFE’s demonstration could be interpreted as hurtful. &lt;strong&gt;We as an Assembly cannot let hurtful words stop us from having important dialogue and from making difficult decisions&lt;/strong&gt;. As U.S. Supreme Court Justice John Marshall Harlan II wrote in his opinion for the 1971 Cohen v. California case, “one man’s vulgarity is another’s lyric.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Representative Arm undoubtedly spoke with heavy emotion when he discussed the demonstration with representatives of SAFE in the Diag. &lt;strong&gt;He spoke passionately, but he remained well inside his First Amendment rights.&lt;/strong&gt; His choice to speak his opinion and demonstrate grievances is not unbecoming of a representative. Representative Arm asked for all students present to take a moment of silence. Representative Arm never identified himself as a representative of Central Student Government. He never attempted speak on behalf of Central Student Government or even mentioned the governing body. He asked SAFE to continue the dialogue at a later point and offered to share his contact information. &lt;strong&gt;He did not curse, nor did he use hateful language. He should not be penalized because he is passionate and cares deeply about this issue. The Ethics Committee encourages students and representatives to continue to passionately and respectfully advocate on behalf of the causes they believe in.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At a time when BDS bullies seem to feel more emboldened to &lt;a href=&quot;http://legalinsurrection.com/2015/11/anti-israel-students-target-ut-austin-israeli-studies-prof-after-disrupting-his-speech/&quot;&gt;disrupt academic events they disagree with&lt;/a&gt; and Jewish and pro-Israel students feel intimidated, this is an incredibly important event. Anti-Israel haters who sought to stifle free speech and expel a pro-Israel student from the student government were resoundingly shut down in the name of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.israellycool.com/2015/11/17/academic-freedom-initiatives/&quot;&gt;academic freedom&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While it is still troubling that the one and only Ethics Probe ever at the University of Michigan was against a Jewish student standing up for Jewish rights, it is heartening to see that not every campus has allowed the radical anti-free speech, anti-Zionist agenda take over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;####Be a part of the conversation at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.israellycool.com/2015/12/08/bdsfail-jewish-student-unanimously-beats-ethics-probe-after-standing-up-to-anti-israel-protesters/&quot;&gt;IsraellyCool&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/12/08/BDSFail-UMichigan/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/12/08/BDSFail-UMichigan/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Why The British Royal Family Won&#39;t Visit Israel</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;At the recent conference on climate change in Paris, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesofisrael.com/british-royals-wont-visit-israel-till-conflict-solved/&quot;&gt;Prime Minister Netanyahu invited Prince Charles to visit Israel&lt;/a&gt;. However, according to a British government source, it will never happen, saying, “Until there is a settlement between Israel and the Palestinian Authority, the Royal family can’t really go there… In Israel so much politics is caught up in the land itself that it’s best to avoid those complications altogether by not going there.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently the sight of a member of the royal family setting foot in Israel would be just too “complicated.” However, Prince Charles and the Queen are very well traveled and don’t seem to have issues overcoming “complications” when it comes to pretty much any other country, so the Judean People’s Front has put together a list of just a few of the countries the British Royals have been able to visit without any difficulty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.princeofwales.gov.uk/the-prince-of-wales/royal-duties/countries-visited&quot;&gt;Charles, Prince of Wales&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/DTyVKOh.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Prince Charles&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bahrain (1986, 1989, 1997, 2007. sorry Shiite majority living under Sunni rule…)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bangladesh (1997)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cyprus (1986, shhh, no one tell the North)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Egypt (1981, 1995, 2006)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Falkland Islands (1999, lo siento la Argentina)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;India (8 times between 1975-2013, sorry Kashmir)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Iran (2004)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Iraq (2004)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ivory Coast (1977)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jordan (1993, 1999, 2004, 2013)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kazakhstan (1996)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kyrgyzstan (1996)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kuwait (1989, 1993, 1997, 2006, 2007, 2011. FYI, Kuwaiti women gained suffrage in 2005…)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Libya (1954)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Morocco (1995, 1996, 1999, 2010)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Nigeria (1990, 1999, 2006)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oman (1985, 1995, 1999, 2003, 2013)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pakistan (2006)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Qatar (1986, 1997, 2007, 2010, 2011, 2013, 2014)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Russia (1994, 2003)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Saudi Arabia (1986, 1990, 1993, 1997, 1999, 2001, 2004, 2005, 2006, 2010, 2013, 2014. Why visit a human rights disaster of a country only once when twelve times will do?)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sri Lanka (1998, 2005, 2013)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Swaziland (1987, 1997)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Turkey (1989, 1993, 1996, 2004, 2005, 2007)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Turkmenistan (1996)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;UAE (1989, 1993, 1996, 1999, 2007)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Uzbekistan (1996)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Venezuela (1978, 1989, 1992)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Yugoslavia (1978)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Zimbabwe (1980)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Prince did come to Israel in 1995 to represent the Queen at Rabin’s funeral (which was also the only time Hosni Mubarak visited as well). I guess the only time it’s ok to come to Israel is when Jews fulfill their true role in the eyes of the West: pitiable corpses. It seems Prince Charles simply does not have time to visit the world’s only Jewish State and the only democracy in the Middle East given his busy schedule meeting with dictators and human rights abusers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Charles also got into some trouble a few years ago when &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/uknews/1569518/Prince-Charles-thrust-into-row-over-Israel.html&quot;&gt;his staff was invited to visit the Knesset&lt;/a&gt;. His aids got into hot water after accidentally CC’ing the Israeli ambassador on internal emails making plain they would never come to Israel because Israel would only want to use the opportunity to bring in His Royal Highness to “burnish its international image,” something the Prince only likes to do for paragons of human rights like Saudi Arabia, Bahrain and Kuwait.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for Her Majesty the Queen, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.royal.gov.uk/MonarchUK/RoyalVisits/OutwardStatevisitssince1952.aspx&quot;&gt;where has she been traveling to&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/18fiuX3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;HRH&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Algeria (1980)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bahrain (1979)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bangladesh (1983)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;China (1986)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;India (1983, 1997)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Iran (1996)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Jordan (1984)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Kuwait (1979)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Liberia (1961)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Maldives (1972)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Morocco (1980)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Qatar (1979)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Oman (1979, 2010)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pakistan (1997)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Russia (1994)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Saudi Arabia (1979)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sri Lanka (1981)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sudan (1965)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tunisia (1980)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Turkey (1971, 2008)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;UAE (1979, 2010)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Yugoslavia (1972)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Zimbabwe (1991)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And where was the Queen’s very first visit abroad all the way back in 1947?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.royal.gov.uk/MonarchUK/RoyalVisits/Overseasvisits.aspx&quot;&gt;Racist British South Africa&lt;/a&gt;, of course. Good thing she won’t come to Israel, it might ruin her image!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Join the conversation on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.israellycool.com/2015/12/08/why-the-british-royal-family-wont-visit-israel/&quot;&gt;IsraellyCool&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/12/07/Why-The-British-Royal-Family-Won't-Visit-Israel/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/12/07/Why-The-British-Royal-Family-Won't-Visit-Israel/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Israel Arrests Jewish Terrorists As Leftist And Arab Parties Freak Out</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Today was a good day for Israeli justice as the police finally announced &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesofisrael.com/israel-arrests-jewish-terror-suspects-in-deadly-firebombing/&quot;&gt;the arrest of several Jewish terrorists&lt;/a&gt; who officials say carried out the attack on the Dawabshe family in Duma back in July that killed four month old Ali and his two parents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, not everyone in Israel welcomed this news. No, it wasn’t the “right-wing extremist settlers” of the Yesha Council who condemned “the heinous crime,” saying, “The acts committed were immoral and harmed the values of the state of Israel and the settlements.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesofisrael.com/opposition-mks-hail-jewish-terror-arrests-knock-lateness/&quot;&gt;the anger came from the Left&lt;/a&gt; who are convinced that, despite not having any information yet due to the continuing gag order, clearly Israel is racist since it foften arrests Arab terrorists quickly but it took longer to arrest these Jewish terrorists. Apparently, according to the Left, arresting someone in the middle of a stabbing attack is just as easy as arresting a secret group of people who attacked a house in the middle of the night leaving almost no clues as to who they were or where they came from. They are also forgetting that the police arrested the Jewish terrorists behind the murder of Muhammad Abu Khedir within a matter of days. No matter, according to them Israel is racist against Arabs so they have to force the facts to fit their preconceived worldview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did Meretz Chairwoman Zahava Gal-on, who said it was”very bad that it took so long” to make the arrests had access to evidence the Israel Police and Shin Bet did not? If so she should be investigated and if not she should not get in the way of police investigations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zouheir Bahloul, the Zionist Union’s token Arab MK from their “minority slot,” apparently thinks that if police can’t make the arrests on the same day, then they shouldn’t even bother since he said the arrests were “too little, too late.” I think we can all be grateful that Bahloul is not in charge of anyone’s security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But perhaps the most “interesting” response to the arrests came from Join Arab List, Hadash MK Yousef Jabareen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/XWvruaQ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jabareen&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than thanking the police for their persistent investigation that has finally born fruit, he decided to exploit the deaths of Baby Ali and his parents to make a political message about the “Occupation.” But his description of the “Occupation” is very telling:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;the main [thing] responsible for the murder is &lt;strong&gt;the occupation that has persisted for nearly 10 decades&lt;/strong&gt;, under whose auspices crimes like this are committed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nearly 10 decades? Israel retook Judea and Samaria nearly 5 decades ago. Israel was reestablished nearly 7 decades ago. But 10 decades ago there was no Israel and no settlements. 10 decades ago there were only Jews living under Ottoman occupation. However, according to Jabareen’s Joint List, the mere presence of Jews is “illegal occupation” and must end. This is all the more shocking given that he is a member of Hadash, the joint Jewish-Arab communist party. If even high ranking Arab members of the party that prides itself on being “the Champion of Jewish-Arab coexistence” conflate even a minor Jewish presence in a Muslim state to be “occupation” then we need to stop being surprised when our peace offers are rejected and our very existence as a Jewish State is denied by others even more extreme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, if Israeli Arabs do not agree with the extremism of Jabareen and the rest of the Joint List, it is about time they formed a party that better represents them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/12/03/100-Year-Occupation/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/12/03/100-Year-Occupation/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>What about the Southern Branch of the Islamic Movement?</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;By now most of you have heard that Israel recently banned the Northern Branch of the Islamic Movement in Israel. Real Jstreets has already discussed the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.israellycool.com/2015/11/17/outlaws-northern-branch-of-islamic-movement/&quot;&gt;radical, anti-Semitic and violent things they have said and supported&lt;/a&gt;. But there is another part of this story that is being brushed under the carpet:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Southern Branch is just as radical, anti-Israel and hate-filled as the Northern Branch!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If that is true, though, then why is it legal and referred to as moderate?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesofisrael.com/israel-bans-islamist-group-saying-its-inciting-violence/&quot;&gt;Times of Israel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The movement split two decades ago. &lt;strong&gt;The more moderate southern branch&lt;/strong&gt; began fielding candidates for Israel’s Knesset in 1996 and is now part of the Joint List, an alliance of several Arab-Israeli political parties. Three of the Joint List’s 13 current Knesset members are part of the movement. &lt;strong&gt;The more hardline northern branch&lt;/strong&gt; rejects any legitimization of Israel’s government and has called on its adherents to boycott elections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s right, the Islamic Movement in Israel split between the “hardliners” in the north who hold the radical Islamist beliefs of the Muslim Brotherhood while boycotting Israeli elections and the “moderates” in the south who hold the radical Islamist beliefs of the Muslim Brotherhood while participating in Israeli elections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did you spot the difference? It is the same difference frequently cited by the media for why ISIS is radical and Hamas is moderate, namely that while they both hold fundamentalist Islamist views that are inherently anti-Semitic, misogynistic, homophobic and expansionist, Hamas has changed its tactics and agreed to participate in elections it knows it can win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/anj2hqX.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Jihad in Palestine&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In “&lt;a href=&quot;https://books.google.com/books?id=xDI-CgAAQBAJ&amp;amp;pg=PA73&amp;amp;lpg=PA73&amp;amp;dq=Hamed+Abu+Daa%27bas&amp;amp;source=bl&amp;amp;ots=MKQIhOefrJ&amp;amp;sig=oJAWW6oSD5A4XzojUoLiVpTSbVk&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sa=X&amp;amp;ved=0CB4Q6AEwAGoVChMI7NaykIObyQIVQZIeCh0hLgB9#v=onepage&amp;amp;q=Hamed%20Abu%20Daa&#39;bas&amp;amp;f=false&quot;&gt;Jihad in Palestine: Political Islam and the Israeli-Palestinian Conflict&lt;/a&gt;” Professor Shaul Bartal of Bar Ilan University explains that there is virtually no difference between the ideology of the two factions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It’s hard to find any difference between the substance of the remarks made by the southern faction [of the Islamic Movement] when compared with those made by the northern faction. (p. 72)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In retrospect, there are not two factions but only one Islamic Movement, and that is the movement of Sheikh Salah. (p. 70)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A careful examination of the newspapers &lt;em&gt;al-Mithaq&lt;/em&gt; of the southern faction and &lt;em&gt;Sawt al-Haq wa-al-Horiya&lt;/em&gt; of the northern faction shows that &lt;strong&gt;there is no ideological difference between the two Israeli factions of the Muslim Brotherhood&lt;/strong&gt; [emphasis JPF]. However, Ra’ed Salah… expressed his anti-Israel stance more strongly. It is no surprise that all Ra’ed Salah’s speeches appear on the different Hamas websites. (p. 73)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even the Southern Branch’s “moderate” decision to participate in elections does not stem from a difference in ideology but is merely a tactical decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;There is mutual reciprocity between all of the Muslim Brotherhood factions as all of them are a part of the Islamic Movement and take sustenance from the same sources. Thus, for example, &lt;strong&gt;both factions of the Islamic Movement in Israel donate funds to the families of Hamas martyrs&lt;/strong&gt; under the category of charity to orphans and widows. &lt;strong&gt;If one judges their declarations, no one disagrees that all the factions are dedicated to the same goal of jihad against Israel and the destruction of the Jewish entity that exists in Palestine.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jihad&lt;/em&gt; can take many different forms - economic, social, legal, through propaganda and also military. All of these means are acceptable in the eyes of the Muslim Brotherhood in order to carry out their goal to establish an Islamic Palestine at the expense of all the territory of the State of Israel. (p. 74-75)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;One of the two founders of Hemmah [The Jersualem Committee for the Prevention of the Destruction and Expulsion Plan], Abd al-Basit Abu al-Mufalfel… in his words, there is no difference between the Muslim Brotherhood, as the mother organization, and Hamas and the Islamic Movement, except from the point of view of the distribution of tasks. (p. 71-72)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that we have established that careful study of the ideology of both factions of the Islamic Movement shows no difference between the two (or Hamas for that matter), let’s examine the words and actions of the Southern Branch’s leading members.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Hamed Abu Daa’bas - Leader of the Southern Branch of the Islamic Movement in Israel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the “split” in the Islamic movement, Hamed Abu Daa’bas joined Raed Salah on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.islamicinvitationturkey.com/2010/06/01/sheikh-raed-salah-not-hurt/&quot;&gt;“Freedom Floatilla” back in 2010&lt;/a&gt; (along with his political partner, the “honorable” Hanin Zoabi).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.memri.org/report/en/print5439.htm&quot;&gt;Daa’bas has also been in talks with Salah&lt;/a&gt; to officially reunite the two branches since 2011 and said he’d be willing to leave the Knesset to accomplish this goal. Perhaps  this will be fulfilled by simply having Salah join the Southern Branch. Time will tell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ynetnews.com/articles/0,7340,L-4568144,00.html&quot;&gt;Daa’bas has also expressed his support for ISIS&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“&lt;strong&gt;ISIS raises reasonable demands like the establishment of an Islamic state&lt;/strong&gt;, but their methods for reaching their objective raise concern in many nations across the world… [however] &lt;strong&gt;ISIS was hurting their cause by filming their cruel and disgusting acts&lt;/strong&gt;. I am against the murders, but it is important to note that the killing methods of Israel and the US are not better than the crimes of the Islamic State. If it were not for the shocking ways in which they kill, it would be possible to see ISIS like any other Jihadi organization.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You read that correctly, according to the leader of the “moderate” branch of the Islamic Movement, it isn’t ISIS’s cruel and disgusting acts themselves that are wrong, but rather the fact that they film them! However, given that Daa’bas and the rest of the Muslim Brotherhood in Israel recognize the importance of tactics and differentiation of their roles in Jihad, this should not be surprising. He does not object to what ISIS does or to its “reasonable” goal of establishing a caliphate, he just wishes they would follow his lead and not always be so open about the violent way they want to accomplish it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Ibrahim Sarsur - Former head of the Southern Branch, former MK and Chairman of the United Arab List&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ynetnews.com/articles/0,7340,L-3537107,00.html&quot;&gt;Sarsur has compared Israelis to Nazis&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Israel’s killing of innocent people is reminiscent of some very dark times, including that of the Nazis.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He has also praised Hezbollah and called for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.israelnationalnews.com/News/News.aspx/144978#.Vk6_DdKrSM8&quot;&gt;establishing a Caliphate in the place of Israel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“there is strength and strategic insight and presence locally and regionally for Hizbullah… They are thinking how to return this fear to Israel and how to destroy Israel’s deterrence, which is the pillar of Israel’s continuation. And if this happens, this means that the line will begin to point extremely downwards for Israel’s deterrence.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Arabic he characterizes Israel as a tool of Western Imperialism to destroy the unity of the Ummah:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“[The West] planted this foreign object [Israel] which does not fit in an eastern Islamic environment, planted it in its heart as to remain as a thorn in their side and a thorn in their throat in order to prevent their [Muslim] unity so as to stop this Islamic giant to take its [historic] position.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But don’t worry, in Hebrew and English he knows the “right” things to say, that is, the exact opposite of what he believes and says in Arabic:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“They [Israeli Jews] should be thinking about me not as a fifth column, but as an integral part of the country who might contribute a lot for the building of this state and might contribute a certain bridge between Israeli Jews and the Arab and Muslim world.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He has also made numerous disparaging comments about Gays and Lesbians while simultaneously asserting there are none in the Muslim community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Masud Ghnaim - Chairman of the United Arab List, Number 2 in the Joint Arab List&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ynetnews.com/articles/0,7340,L-3887468,00.html&quot;&gt;Ghnaim is also a strong supporter of replacing Israel with a caliphate&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“an Islamic caliphate should be established and it should include Israel… I believe there is an urgent need to return to the Islamic caliphate. I believe this is the most fitting solution to the state of weakness, deterioration and erosion the Arabs and Muslims are suffering from,”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He also has nothing but praise for Hezbollah, Iran and Syria in their fight against Israel:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“I am against any aggression and any alliance that does not serve the Arab interest. I support the righteous party. The Iran-Hezbollah-Syria axis represents the line of resistance and intractability, and naturally, I support this axis. Hezbollah is the security valve of the residents of Lebanon. Hassan Nasrallah has properly combined the political and religious plan.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Talab Abu Arar - Number 9 in the Joint Arab List&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to being a bigamist who &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Arab-MK-found-to-be-member-of-infidelity-website-ashleymadisoncom-412540&quot;&gt;had a confirmed email on Ashley Madison&lt;/a&gt; Abu Arar is also a supporter of the &lt;a href=&quot;http://english.palinfo.com/site/pages/details.aspx?itemid=73502&quot;&gt;Murabitun and Murabitat&lt;/a&gt; bullies sent by the Northern Branch to harass Jews on the Temple Mount… but according to him, they just stage sit-ins!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He is also very clear that Jews and all non-Muslims should not be allowed to visit the Temple Mount, saying “Al-Aqsa is for Muslims; never for anyone else.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;###Abd al-Hakim Hajj Yahya - Number 2 in the Islamic Movement political party, Number 6 in the Joint Arab List&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yahya accompanied fellow Joint List MK, Jamal Zahalka, during his visit to the Temple Mount when &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesofisrael.com/this-is-not-yours-arab-mk-yells-at-jews-on-temple-mount/&quot;&gt;he verbally abused visiting Jews&lt;/a&gt; yelling:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Crazy criminals, you’re all Kahanists, fascists, racists, get out of here, you hurt Muslims. This is my home. You need to get out of my house. You put crazies in here. You have no god.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jns.org/news-briefs/2015/7/27/temple-mount-arabs-attack-jews-and-police-with-rocks-and-firebombs-on-tisha-beav#.Vk7LGdKrSM8=&quot;&gt;Back in July&lt;/a&gt;, he visited the Temple Mount with Ghnaim and Abu Arar to protest what the “warlike” atmosphere caused by “extremist warmongering settlers who are trying to change the status quo in every way.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the Islamic Movement’s open rejection of the Jewish and democratic characters of the State of Israel and its leaders support for terrorist groups and enemy states against the country in whose parliament they serve, it is beyond surprising that the Southern Branch is legal at all. The State would not need to prove its connections to Hamas (which are just as strong as that of the Northern Branch), just that it is in violation of Basic Law: The Knesset Section 7A “Prevention of participation of candidates list.” This actually happened back in 2006, but &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ynetnews.com/articles/0,7340,L-3660120,00.html&quot;&gt;the Supreme Court overturned the decision&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can you imagine what would happen if a Jewish political party openly spoke about replacing Israel with a rabbinic state, advocated expelling Arabs and supported banned Jewish terrorist organizations? Is there any chance such a party would be called moderate and allowed to run? You don’t have to imagine because the Kach and Kahane Chai parties did just that and were subsequently banned from running for Knesset and outlawed as terrorist organizations themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Israel did the right thing by banning these extremist Jewish parties and it is about time it did the same by applying the law equally to their Arab extremist cousins in the Southern Branch of the Islamic Movement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/11/20/Islamic-Movement/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/11/20/Islamic-Movement/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>The Judean People&#39;s Front is now on IsraellyCool</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;We just wanted to announce that the Judean People’s Front has been invited to join the great team over at &lt;a href=&quot;www.israellycool.com&quot;&gt;IsraellyCool&lt;/a&gt;. The JPF will continue to post here but we encourage you to head over to IsraellyCool as well to check out our posts and the many other great pro-Israel articles there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a great day for the JPF!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
</description>
				
				<pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<link>http://judeanpf.com/2015/11/17/IsraellyCool/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://judeanpf.com/2015/11/17/IsraellyCool/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>